<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lead on ossem: a creative space</title>
    <link>/boxes/lead/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lead on ossem: a creative space</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/boxes/lead/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Two</title>
      <link>/words/2014/two/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2014/two/</guid>
      <description>Encased in Her desire
I am dressed in Mire.
Second-face
Throughport
Who has second center?
Would you like to sleep?
Essence, pre-absorbed.
She’s in my hind-center.
Images are cheap
A dozen, so to speak.
A mouthpiece is necessary
Will you marry me?
The secret is out
Without a doubt.
And a stop goes to
A cottonmouth.
No play
To this day
We are in the south
Don’t bounce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Please</title>
      <link>/words/2014/please/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2014/please/</guid>
      <description>She breathes in my opposite Counterbearing to my darewit, She billows in gallows far from me. And I, in esteem, carry streets of dreams Collective arms and nations. Breathe. I am the ends of me. D96 Premonitions are not unlost. We peer into the sanctuary. We are in the posthaste mortuary. Songs are written, foes are beaten. Adversaries tell the tale, warriors ring the bell. Short-timers sell, Cretans foretell. An ocean for a lover, Conscious compromise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ton</title>
      <link>/words/2014/ton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2014/ton/</guid>
      <description>Into me. Breathe. q. Breathe deep. I construct theis guy. Neurotic hackery? A piece of me. Is there anything wrong? Is there anything right? Of f to the ocorner of ahthatht guy. Let’s’ hit that; Let’s do. I might migraine to the 2nd soul. I might be in your room. In our room. I omight. Sencidn., Interview.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T</title>
      <link>/words/2014/t/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2014/t/</guid>
      <description>To give carely. To receive bountifully. We are the psychology of you. And us. The aisles of contempt. And anguish. Your Love is here. Be clear. The trips of dreams In me. The obsession of wealth. The obsession of Time. The trips within me Are beam. A smoky horizon, Breeding impermanence. A dangerous occupation. In the flesh, You’re letting your work run in. The work runs in within I’ll trail after that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trust</title>
      <link>/words/2013/trust/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/trust/</guid>
      <description>When She cries in me. (I am insane). And the words we make. (are just a game). How does one go mad? (sure you’re not glad?) Is it a suit and bow tie? (don’t forget to die). How do I channel you? (you’re still living). How do I level you? (you’re still breathing). These words we use. (are just a game). Mystery tells. (another story). A space to His own. (it’s His kingdom, after all).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tramp</title>
      <link>/words/2013/tramp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/tramp/</guid>
      <description>A god, Broken into billions of pieces. A piece is you. To gather the pieces is… a clue. Are you a piece of me? Am I a piece of you? How do I see this piece of me? Where? Shattered. Assembled whole. Ocean images. You must show something for your efforts. Something. There are trysts in these parts. There are trusts, too. I have the karma divide. She is not very nice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tempt</title>
      <link>/words/2013/tempt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/tempt/</guid>
      <description>I is the drink. Do I get paid to think? Cummervescence. Pleasance. Trysto. Manifesto. Where is the mindset? Where is the bodytet? No Pain. No Fear. Play your hand. It’s in the sand. What’s air to you? Just asking. Air is nice. It’s not ice. My crazy little friend. Chipzah. To me, it means prosperity. See, I dance around. Unexpopound(ed). And when the moon’s not right. We solicify it. Same ol’ me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep</title>
      <link>/photos/deep/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photos/deep/</guid>
      <description>Burning my copy of Garbage and the Goddess, as instructed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tea</title>
      <link>/words/2013/tea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/tea/</guid>
      <description>In my state. Counting. 0000000000000. T-state? Is this an edge push or not? An edgue –push state? (Demonstration?) A pish. A puwsh. A blinding. Push spiy. Spoy.. Qqqqqq believing., And onccccccce a;; beliving is done. A student of crime. Now, that’s the first thing that’s mmade sense…. Thru. These broken deade keyboards, The then sealed. Your eyes. Open.d. Miracle. Whart. Is the message. Pretenser. Pretenser? What is the mesaage? Q	whqat is your messsaagwe?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Short</title>
      <link>/words/2013/short/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/short/</guid>
      <description>Are you crying? Are you dead? Order. Prestigue. sAfter all that… Yoiur at a hakter, Is nthere an aex”? Your study yoouuuur ahit/. Youuuuve been preshifted. Is that goofd? You habve n o understanding. Ill dance to me. T m humanity.\ \\	\	\\\	\\ Well. It’s us;. You’re such a chhhhhhhhhhhhheater. Flesh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dirt</title>
      <link>/words/2013/dirt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/dirt/</guid>
      <description>Strike a dime’s eye. It’s your might. Are we children? Or are we dancers? A child dances upon leaves. Who are we? Figure it out. A cold doubt. We are the Kings and Queens of Mystery Eternal. A golden sun upon yourself. Am I you? Am I him? (frame). Deny the God upon your servant’s brow. In your head are we? Then what are we here for? I fold my eyelid over itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rock</title>
      <link>/photos/rock/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photos/rock/</guid>
      <description>Page 87 of Garbage and the Goddess. What struck me about this image was the overwhelmingly male energy presented in the foreground of this photo with a powerful-looking female in the background, somehow keeping everyone in check. I sketched my own variation of this photo here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rock</title>
      <link>/sketches/rock/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sketches/rock/</guid>
      <description>My interpretation of page 87 from Garbage and the Goddess. In the background hangs The Great Wave of Kanagawa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bring</title>
      <link>/words/2012/bring/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/bring/</guid>
      <description>And fell, the hammer did fell. The pressure, misfit. Hey, did you just make that? It’s my art, so yes. Side room. Is this side room ours? ? Wow. You stretched it. (hard). Why won’t you hit your heart? A dance of pleasure. Aced of bacon. A slide show. Prescence. Hey,. That’s wrong. Cornerstone is set. Hm, Milk and gasoline. (set us free). Where’s the pleasure principle? TELL ME! The guided crosses will know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ask</title>
      <link>/words/2012/ask/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/ask/</guid>
      <description>It’s a dead end rodeo. Which way will you go. I choose peace. I choose mayhem. That’s funny. That’s not where you were Seconds ago. Tell you what. (we’ll flip a coin). Flip One. (here it goes). Flip two (here’s his campaign manager). Flip three. (here’s to you and me). Get that out of your system? Grind and mind, actually. I’m sure. OK? A protective bith slap… Is he,… watching his language?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Be</title>
      <link>/words/2012/be/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/be/</guid>
      <description>How do you dissolve nerousis? With a toothpick. Now, dance with me. I ain’t hitting that with a glass case. Now a vase. Heyyy! Get it! (alignment) Just being honest. Now, back to that honesty. Does it cost you? There’s a price, isn’t there? Watch the table. TH e table is ours. What do you see? A beautiful song. So not right. What do you hear? An anthem. Now we’re rockin’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tame</title>
      <link>/words/2012/tame/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/tame/</guid>
      <description>In my dreams
I am tucked in Her sleep.
Awakened. Silenced.
In Her fears
She is brought to silenced knee.
A knee to here?
So far from me.
Wet. The streets are soaked.
And the drain is dazed.
Honeyphazed.
A prerecording.
A sonboarding.
A boundary.
A dance space.
In this place, a secret message.
In this family, a tone is set.
Dry rock.
You mean an ice cold precipice
Rock solid can challenge the rights up here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cave</title>
      <link>/words/2012/cave/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/cave/</guid>
      <description>Your brain is hot. Ot’s thinking. A pressure monet. A pressure taking. Is this your wallet. Is this your monhey. Hahaha… I disagree. Who is that guy anyways? Well, I’ll tell you a story. Blah blah, Should you disrupt that one. Thos one. Well politics. Politics are fun. Now, where did the humor go? My humor? Your humour? The humor is here. You watched him as a necessary element. Let me place this base.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beach</title>
      <link>/words/2012/beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/beach/</guid>
      <description>Chipper chapper. Let’s stop this right here. Isn’t this the same as the last? Twelve hours at a time is a long time To read minds. Isn’t it nice to be around people again? To what end? What’s your purpose. To me, Everyone Is poetry. Dancing energy. Your spirit is captured in me. You’re keeping note of names, I like that. Letters, spelling. A nice chat. On a sunny afternoon. The 10:10 would appreciate that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Same</title>
      <link>/words/2012/same/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/same/</guid>
      <description>That was my card. That was our card. She flipped it on its face. I knew it before we grabbed it. The hobbit post-faced it. Row of ladies on the left. Row of guys on the right. Fat bastard’s in my chair The queen’s gotta pair. It’s time to go. It’s time to row. 9:07PM specifically. The trees are leaves. Our eyes met. Consistently. An eye-five. Pleased me. She asked my name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fine</title>
      <link>/words/2012/fine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/fine/</guid>
      <description>When she smiles They, smile. It makes me wonder why I feel this way. And all the connections, and emotions. To deal with them. In your way. And my way. There are very bad things in this world. Very good things, too. Which ones do you choose? We continue to choose both. Imbalance would be treason. If “they” know everything about you, What is there to fear? To be ashamed? To be guilty of?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gut</title>
      <link>/words/2012/gut/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/gut/</guid>
      <description>Answer the question, Claire. There’s an act in all of us. So then, you’re not a … What was the question again? That’s funny, I forgot the question as well. So what are we doing here? Seeking truth. I’m seeking destruction. Hot. Cold. Up. Down. Left Right White Black Peace Trouble Treble Bass Spirit Soul Light Sound Science Art Life Religion Normalcy Anxiety Honesty Trixstery Light Shadow Flattery Stealing Child Adult Adult Child Correcting Cheating Principle Law Good Great Slow Fast Self Phenomena</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I</title>
      <link>/words/2012/i/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/i/</guid>
      <description>I’ll step into your garden While following my bliss. Bliss, while misunderstood, is just a property of your path. It’s a compensation of thinking. That is: feeling. Back to your garden: There is a circle. There are two trees. Twins, I’d say. And then there’s this creepy shed. The leaves paint a path outside of the circle. All the while, I keep my eye steady for the people that might approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let</title>
      <link>/words/2012/let/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/let/</guid>
      <description>How do I live up to this? Looking to the side stage. My Stage. You caught it, you bought it. I’m flipping caps here. I don’t think I can dance this stepfloor. … and then… “I’m sort of interested in honesty.” Ya, what is honesty, anyways? Honesty is reaching for the wrong bottle. And knowing it. Honesty is predicting the future. Then facing it. Honesty is consistency. Didn’t you say that consistency is key?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sell</title>
      <link>/words/2012/sell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/sell/</guid>
      <description>What are your signs? Would I invite Her to church? There’s a roundwheel going around here. Flow the spigot. The spigot is good. Spigggots are also nice, as well. ARE WE IN HELL??? A flower will suit you well. But next time, the flower is there. Not here. All of these multitudes of possibilities. Your area is weak. Where are these starstruck adventures as youth? UNCOMPROMISING, SIR???\ Well, philosophy is one thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time</title>
      <link>/words/2011/time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/time/</guid>
      <description>Here I am The king of my own very canal. A thought Impulse. A derision. Cloudy thoughts. Enter the mindtrain. The purity of extra thought. Loud and clear. An extra ear. Of yours. No way are you here. No way. Strike my hand. Will it bleed. Surface cut. If there is a problem here, I … Chasm of pronouncement. There’s this angle. And this image. And then… A great thought over here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Land</title>
      <link>/words/2011/land/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/land/</guid>
      <description>Will be times. Many times in my life. Where I will simply tone out. Zone out. It’s as if I’m the bell. And the window. It’s as if this is it.	This is all I have. And then I’m called back. A blink. A mystery. A challenge. And then it all seems so foolish. Second guessing. Neighborhooding. Bringing back the last days. Some days. These days. It’s not here. You wish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sand</title>
      <link>/words/2011/sand/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/sand/</guid>
      <description>A cool effervescence Of some sort. Don’t do what you do. Do what you do. To me, There are two forces in life, There’s the reptile And there’s the Space Angel === The art of these two warring fractions Is you. What does it mean To be free? A free man. Last time I checked. There are lots of definitions of free. We’re not gonna get there, are we? Someone over here says… Sin virtue and vice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Line</title>
      <link>/words/2011/line/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/line/</guid>
      <description>Sting serpentine ritual High accord She sung to me Her song. I uh just form here. And then. Magic happen. In this space. Where we were once. Proud and Independent. Without the aid of others. Spiral happenstance. A dance. Mm. Wings unfurl. On the outset.-ide. Oh, you want me to finish this sentence? Well, I have been known to plow forth. To break the seal Of a sacrifice. It’s a big deal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crack</title>
      <link>/words/2011/crack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/crack/</guid>
      <description>Check one check two. They comin’ for you. Check it thrice. Gawd damn. Sir, that’s not very nice. Cup the hands. Now. Straight up. Saw that action. Fire fire. No pants here. If there were, Well, The dashes and mashes. Goodness gracious. Can you imagine? We can. Our crew can. And we do. What’s it to you? Back and forth. See-saw. It’s a bit of a mystery Like fire. Once it catches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Say</title>
      <link>/words/2011/say/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/say/</guid>
      <description>Let’s walk over this tripwire. It’s a finewire. Superfire. Dancestep. Aged regret. Don’t talk yet. Moon dance. Hunted stance. Wolves in the background. And by our side. Simple outlets. Forced blocks. Don’t knock. Home base. Troubled base. A friend of who’s friend? On this battleground. It might be sound. But. I don’t get it. Ya, me too. Why would I keep you closer. If you’re my brother. And all that jazz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lo</title>
      <link>/words/2011/lo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/lo/</guid>
      <description>Something happened. Before it pretenseed. Super yawning. That’s right… magic. Let’s not change the super charged. SUPER CALIFLOWERPRELIOUS Since you asked. Jesuits wished they had the same. Precedence as this. It’s a matter. Of listening To the sky wishing it were shy. And then a mishmash. Supper. Eggs and cheese. Q wish you were me. From so far away? We’re done here. Yay then. Meet and then Meat too. Sausage and chicken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ton</title>
      <link>/words/2011/ton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/ton/</guid>
      <description>Yo dawg I was watching this fly right In my room And it just straight up gave me an Ego Butt To let me know who’s dawg, yo. Alright ok… let’s step away from that one for just a second. I sort of set things up in just.\ Up. Quadrants. If you please. Um. Um Um. Yum Yum Yum. Tum tum tum. Yes? Huh? Huh? Ok. Let’s get right into this shading business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cope</title>
      <link>/words/2011/cope/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/cope/</guid>
      <description>Something mightily going on with this Virgo business. and then the rest of us. We might pee on another man’s teepee? Let’s just get that one out of the way. There’s a predisposition to attend. You know. Like the kind you used to. Some might consider it… Who are these “some” ? Are they the new “They?” … How did you sleep last night? Quite mightily I must say. Was it assisted?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drive</title>
      <link>/words/2011/drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/drive/</guid>
      <description>Secrets are fun. Secrets in this one. There’s a certain. Rope. A dope. Sucka. Played. And now you. On the sidewalk. Cheek against Steel and concrete. Messy barriers. I’m sure they won’t Be harassing us no more. If you cut a tree in two? What will it do? Will it dance? Prance? .. I know the answer to this one. Look outside your window. Will you? Seriously. Check it out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test</title>
      <link>/words/2011/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/test/</guid>
      <description>What does it mean to take a knee? Will you watch it with me? There’s a deeper meaning in Everything that we do. A correspondence. A coalescence. When you sit there. And test the boundaries of others. There’s a certain prospect. Of rejection. When this rejection becomes part of you. You stand upon a pedestal of Perspective. When this perspective has sat upon you. You know your place. Now then, Let us continue?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nick</title>
      <link>/words/2011/nick/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/nick/</guid>
      <description>Littleindaaaaaaaaaaaaan chief. Let’s be brief. There’s a certain. Perspective. Some would say they miss you. Under some tissue. And if that tissue is you? Would you presumpuouptuous new? Now now see? These parts. You’ve never seen. These are some children. Mistresses. Something. Become of this? It’s this code. You might see, Once twice? Want to see more? FUCK YOUR SICOMORE TREE!! YOU WANT THIS PRESENCE??? Child please. Present your Bissom belly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shake</title>
      <link>/words/2011/shake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/shake/</guid>
      <description>A caged animal. Markings on the floor Indicate A separate subsidy Of consolidation. Friends. A plenty. The evidence suggests Brutal undertakings Of a swift investment Only to be turned over Into a long-term contingent. Separately, there seems to be a motion Of an activity /// where was we? There’s something of a phenomena with this process. Maybe you get this. You have your first thought. And then there’s a second. And then another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arc</title>
      <link>/words/2011/arc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/arc/</guid>
      <description>Step Four. Nothing more. Nothing less. Universe can be explained to you. To me. Your answer is your key. It’s simple. Masterpiece. A matter of relativity. You hold in your hands this matter. It’s a silver platter. Subject to respect Circumspection Restoration. Your spirit holds The inseminated images Of cinema. Unfolding your mind In a myriad of different fathoms. A bird’s beak is a delicate name, madam. In this Scorpio’s nest, a Brother brings his best.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snow</title>
      <link>/words/2011/snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/snow/</guid>
      <description>Second step. Let’s place me and you In your shoes. What do you choose? Child You are a foster Fire. In this space. Time for this Party To be a tardy prostitute. Dare I solute. To your mighty Promiscuous ways. But, darling please. What does Prometheus weigh? You might kiss to begin. But this breakfast has already committed sin. The stars in your eyes. Much obliged. Hold and Grant your authorship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Air</title>
      <link>/words/2011/air/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/air/</guid>
      <description>What is this life I lead. Is it a disease. A second ease. Slowly. Slowly. Patience is a virtue. Yes. Have I made a monster out of this? A rubbing of the chaos. First step. Let us begin. It’s something of an underbelly. A fatboy in disguise. Running after his demise. He wishes his wisdom Buried in broken tides. There are spirits in these Trees. Not just you. Not just me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saint</title>
      <link>/words/2011/saint/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/saint/</guid>
      <description>Do you here pronounce these hands To enjoy The placement of space and time. To embrace the holy remembrance Of the Holy white. To Eat the air. To feel the prenumbrance Of You. Together. United. Let’s watch both of you dance Unto the Holy Lights. Let us place you in A Mighty Delight. Be Blessed and Welcomed To Our Kindred. Bringing you in our heed. A supple steed. Let us all pronounce you Light unto All.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>vIEW</title>
      <link>/words/2011/view/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/view/</guid>
      <description>How do I start this. Let us depart this. It’s a supple reality Full of fruits and authority. Can you not take this precious dance Too far. Encased in tar. Embarrassment too far? Let’s take a step back and review. Some view this Extraordinary behavior what does it take to make a band Of three. Might take me. Thee Some authority. AND WHEN YOU PRESS Regress. A gentle neck There’s a certain story here I’m sure it’s in the clear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shy</title>
      <link>/words/2006/shy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/shy/</guid>
      <description>(an)	Ha ha. Not so obvious… Hot white Starlight She doesn’t blink seem Hm.	To me. Trouble is	let’s talk a while. Trouble does. Somewhere in pull up a chair	Here.	pull your hair This pasture.	Her eyes are… Did she just say that?	What is this that I just found myself in… Seems dark And bright At the same time.	Well that was that. It is what it is. Telltale mysteries come to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mean</title>
      <link>/words/2006/mean/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/mean/</guid>
      <description>Snap Pop Pop Snapple Something broke Inside of her Something hooked Whoa. Me me me. He He He. e e e Lettuce play. Verbage Of Nothing. Nothing is something. That&amp;#39;s the best I got. Suffered within that s t a t e o f m I n d State of mine. Mine mine mine. That&amp;#39;s when she smiles. And I crack. Under that bridge of ours. Can I borrow a dollar?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prick</title>
      <link>/words/2006/prick/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/prick/</guid>
      <description>the twins are talking to the scales again as you see and read the time has come to explore some more. whether you are on b o a r d o1r n2o3t. quiver.sliver.river. thistimethistimethistime. silver? more on board this time. there is more balance this time. I have learned. this time. sometimes riddles abound and riddles abound in me the sorcerer&amp;#39;s sword rests in willowed wake. across the pond in the seas a quest it does make.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>