<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Steel on ossem: a creative space</title>
    <link>/boxes/steel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Steel on ossem: a creative space</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/boxes/steel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>One</title>
      <link>/words/2017/one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2017/one/</guid>
      <description>I’ve got a dark eye, yeah. Dipped in marrow. Coated in chaos. Thumbing the lies. Offensive as life. Bathed in bliss. Harnessed in heart. She’s got dark eyes, yeah. Steeped in hallow. Stringing the skies. Suggestive as life. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Since</title>
      <link>/words/2016/since/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2016/since/</guid>
      <description>Something happened in the valley. The strange, and derelict. There are the words to say, to convey. A passing mind’s eye, a mighty shift. Tapestries are folded, in the flock of fools, Sewn together by raging stools. An adventure cut short, only to be abounded, And hounded, by pride and envy. A nature’s wrath comes full force, Only to beg for mercy. A time’s unwind, through space and twine, These are the mystery’s take, through due wine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stake</title>
      <link>/words/2015/stake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2015/stake/</guid>
      <description>Will you not let me be?
(Causal factions)
And if we are not here.
(not in the clear).
It’s not often we are here.
And when I lose the spot we were in,
I become unglued.
The Saints are not happy
With how I play the game.
But to me, it’s all the same.
Battlefields are won with
Patience and poise.
Not reckless noise.
We make a life out of mystery</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pound</title>
      <link>/words/2015/pound/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2015/pound/</guid>
      <description>We are dark. We are deep. We are discrete. She leads me into the mystery. The misery. The ease. Sum of the parts. And the ton. Hash of the gold. Blue hush. Blinded by the metaled bye. Her harsh belt slighted a soft cheek. A family. Tumultuous. Second hindquadrant. Precious immigration. Disguise my blinded eye. She is here. In my clear. How do I hold you? The fear is real. Every night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saved</title>
      <link>/words/2015/saved/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2015/saved/</guid>
      <description>Where hare you?
Are you in the blue.
Are you here in the stead.
Are you here in my head.
I feel the taste.
Electric paste.
The moment between moments.
A calm buzz.
A careening presumption.
A black white hum.
Subtle space.
Can you feel me?
It’s a special space.
A 12 step process.
Five planting.
7 climbing.
Somewhere it is there.
I wear it briefly.
A sudden god.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plot</title>
      <link>/words/2015/plot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2015/plot/</guid>
      <description>She speaks in soft whispers
And I take the messages from
It
And place the binding in you.
Here
She rests in Peace
And confounding bliss
Spires of beauty
Entwined in me.
She’s a part of you, too.
An awkward tirade of sorts
She conspires agenda.
To what was.
What once will be.
Her pleasure is yours.
Will you not act
Upon your time.
I will not.
Singular or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tote</title>
      <link>/words/2014/tote/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2014/tote/</guid>
      <description>So far away
The sun beams
Steal us away
In concrete gutters
We skip and play
So wasted
You sell houses
And I am a wealthy
Prospective buyer
We stroll down heavy
Streets and look over
Cobble-stone driveways
Maybe we&amp;rsquo;ll find a match
And will live happily ever
After and after
Oh look a church
How saintly and
Majestic
Shelled in stained glass
We walk around but
Do not enter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slight</title>
      <link>/words/2014/slight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2014/slight/</guid>
      <description>when the lovers dance
And are swept by
Guiding glances of
Sad sunlight
The gods simple mocking
Of afternoon pleasures
Holidays that are never
Realized.
They
Came to stay. Led astray.
They
Lie awake. Stranded takes.
Misty ghosts dance upon
Misty houses broken down
They laugh and flee.
There is no glee.
A coward&amp;rsquo;s paradise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Break</title>
      <link>/words/2014/break/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2014/break/</guid>
      <description>She stirs in the wind. She sits at my foot and we drift. In consecrated skies, we kiss. She is no home to me. She is so mean to me. Judged, on a half-steak makes me break. I ascend into Her calm. She takes me as I am. She is no savior. And when I commune with Her, Universes dissipate with Bright. She teaches how to hold my sword. And I learn how to make my word.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bow</title>
      <link>/words/2014/bow/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2014/bow/</guid>
      <description>When She kisses my moonlight, I hide in burrowed screams. And I, in my own light. Know Her sunbeams. My worthless plight of day. Her might of play. Taunting. The Earth bends below Her. It sings joyed terror. And I, in my dance. Lurch in acquiesce. Stupidity rinses my strength away. Down such a gloried fade. Days of promise seem so far away. No angels stand near. Knocks of wine. Colors spin so fine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pure</title>
      <link>/words/2013/pure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/pure/</guid>
      <description>Thoughts and dreams… and mystery. She sings to me With Such Broken Promises. I cling to Her twisted stains. For my life. (in disbelief) In terror, I am Her puppet. In life, I am Her master. In troubled keep. I dance Her wake. I wrap myself in Her mistakes. For Her misery is my desire. A steadfast plan of mire. And desolate beauty. Seen. Lost in Her seams. I long for Her lonely glance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Try</title>
      <link>/words/2013/try/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/try/</guid>
      <description>She lights my world. In me. And i. am. Hers. I echo through Her landscape. Her sounds bound in bliss. Lighted by fire. Seething The Bright. I slide down Her magnificent high. And then She becomes me. The absurdity. I reign Her chaos so suddenly. We grasp upon the signs of dance. I am drowned in Her expanse. We celebrate the Godspace. Broken like bread on a tree’s face. She whispers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thing</title>
      <link>/words/2013/thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/thing/</guid>
      <description>A lover’s space, A hint of the unthinkable. A chord of trust. A messenger in God’s space. A forsaken plan. A song of pain. A coward’s trace, A trace of the predictable, A patio’s preface. A repetitive apology. A muse speaks. A maze breaks. A dance turns to words. A word turns to God. A riddle becomes God. A solution begins, A friendship trends, A team mends. A cycle of truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stand</title>
      <link>/words/2013/stand/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/stand/</guid>
      <description>She’s got a dirty eye Placed in me She’s got a filthy spirit Dancing A dirty eye Not far from peace A filthy spirit Pleasing A time comes Wrapped in strands Of stars And rapture Her voice Here Her space Vision Entering upon the Sun Joining my broken body Pieces and dust Mixed destiny Stirred vastness I am Her wasted soldier Sword in broken hand I tremble Fortified She seals me Forged in night She takes me Shadows breaking sand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Link</title>
      <link>/words/2012/link/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/link/</guid>
      <description>And here. We are beautifully broken. So perfectly lost. How did we get here? So fairytale. A lost ship has sunk. From its coast, it dares not tell. Angels swoop upon the treasure. (it is their pleasure) Collect the gold. It’s greed, after all. Timeless classic. Pace a time’s forth. (are you in love again?) There is something to be bought. A price that is sought. There are stories to be won.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Line</title>
      <link>/words/2012/line/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/line/</guid>
      <description>Well, I&amp;rsquo;ve got
The world in my eyes and
The Universe in my Heart
I&amp;rsquo;m not sure where to start
Maybe with you.
We&amp;rsquo;ll ride the blue
Break the clear
Ride the clear
Run the fear
Be the fear
In your presence
The choice is clear
I&amp;rsquo;m your terrorist
I&amp;rsquo;m your hero
I&amp;rsquo;m the everything
You don&amp;rsquo;t know
I&amp;rsquo;m the terrorist
I&amp;rsquo;m the hero
There&amp;rsquo;s no telling
The seed I sow</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set</title>
      <link>/words/2012/set/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/set/</guid>
      <description>The Sun sets, yet,
The World in Her Eyes
The Wings of Her Flight
The Sun sets, yet.
The Sun sets, yet,
The dare to change
The Air of Change
The Sun sets, yet.
The Sun sets, yet,
The nation of sorrow
The heart of tomorrow
The Sun sets, yet.
The Sun sets, yet,
The happiness within Her
The peace beneath Her.
The Sun sets, yet.
The Sun sets, yet,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trim</title>
      <link>/words/2012/trim/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/trim/</guid>
      <description>Heated dance. Billowing hair. Her look. In my locked cell. She gives me grace. Spaced shoulders. Pumping… This is her crowd. By the hand, She takes me. I feel her sweat. Her heat takes me. Jumping, Her look. unfolds my world. And the way she is Makes me wonder what will be. Supple responsibility. In here. We are partners. Assembled whole. A problem is just a label. We see the stage for what it is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chain</title>
      <link>/words/2012/chain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/chain/</guid>
      <description>Chained.
Behind blacked walls.
A screen appears.
She appears to me.
Human form.
Speaking. On authority.
And now, the quest begins.
An innerspace of wills.
To read the ether.
To provide the circumstance.
The mist dissolves in sunlight.
Tremendous bright.
Her energy radiates beauty.
Dissipating lock and key.
And here. In our time.
We play the tones of life.’
And wonder the keys and charms within.
Can I make this better?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sense</title>
      <link>/words/2012/sense/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/sense/</guid>
      <description>Well, she’s a righteous shortcoming I want to be her. To dance her. To lick her skin deep within She knows my heartache (It’s a sick mistake.) I can’t break her trust I must trip in her eyes It’s no surprise Her heart tries to capture That what is in me When I soak in the ripples of her bliss I cannot dismiss that I No longer No longer No longer Know me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rhyme</title>
      <link>/words/2012/rhyme/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/rhyme/</guid>
      <description>I gauged her thighs carefully. Broken skirt. Her paw had summit. I fathomed a conversation. But instead I settled into Her. Gauging again. I watch her thighs. She sees my moves. I reangle. WAY overcompensate. She flees. At the sight of me. Hands clawing. Turn right. Into left. Mirror passes pillar. She peeks past plastic star. Am I too far? Too distant? I drive. Not too fast. Not too slow. But there’s a jacket on the car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gift</title>
      <link>/words/2012/gift/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/gift/</guid>
      <description>The cars sound empty And hollow. The band swings mighty hallowed. We walk with saints. She’s the lead singer. Man she can belt a tune. And there’s the story teller. Telling your fortunes. A roving band. Walking the streets of netherland. Strange talent of gods. Speak with us. Calling / sparking / presence. Man, let’s load up on the spirits. Poets of concrete. No longer discrete. Where did you get that shirt?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plain</title>
      <link>/words/2011/plain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/plain/</guid>
      <description>I saw it. No. You had it wrong. You can slay something. And you can love something. It’s not the same, Gentlemen. Can we go back to ground zero. What is this hero’s business anyways? Consciousness? Ego? OK. Once there was this Dragon. It lived in its nest. A far-reaching cliff of sorts. Now this Dragon was very natural In how it behaved. It flew the skies of paradise. High brow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brace</title>
      <link>/words/2011/brace/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/brace/</guid>
      <description>The Warrior sits upright With his sword belted Tightly. He brings his chest to bare. Something of a precious artifact. The swinging Indian scout drops over his stout log A bit of a fog. Over the horizon there’s a Message from the cul-de-sac. The Warrior. Grasps his handle. Darkened wisp of candle. He clings. Nightly. &amp;#34;Shouldn’t your majesty be. Twisting a different message?&amp;#34; The swinging Indian scout. Laughs wildly. The others are just.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pass</title>
      <link>/words/2011/pass/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/pass/</guid>
      <description>I touch the mindstream.
I feel the chaos.
I peel your fervor.
I am your velvet.
Trickle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twice</title>
      <link>/words/2011/twice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/twice/</guid>
      <description>Pouted mouth suckles
Loaded metal
Dagger.
Make it come baby.
Too late.
Gray wake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Once</title>
      <link>/words/2011/once/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/once/</guid>
      <description>She&amp;rsquo;s happiest
When&amp;rsquo;s she&amp;rsquo;s weightless
Drifting into gray Depths.
Heartless laughter.
Tribal disaster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grime</title>
      <link>/words/2011/grime/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/grime/</guid>
      <description>Shaking paw.
High desire.
Her noted palace.
Mire.
Notes and color.
Introduction and mayhem.
It&amp;rsquo;s a feud of mother.
Father.
Let&amp;rsquo;s battle this brother.
To the Technicolor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mow</title>
      <link>/words/2011/mow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/mow/</guid>
      <description>Her soul is desolate.
Her angel is a liquid slate.
Here and now.
A placement of soul
Shifting Netherlands.
She has the key as Her sword.
I watch Her weep brightly, foreword.
And then her.
&amp;ndash; her dagger runs deep in dreamscape
I awake in a bloody escape.
Where does her slithering organ end?
Not a friend. Here everything
is below board.
Soaring before.
And now
Not so clear.
Some fear in those crystal</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shred</title>
      <link>/words/2011/shred/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/shred/</guid>
      <description>She sits with me
Full tilt as the sidewalk
Melts between us
Dirty devils steal one of us
She&amp;rsquo;s a sidearm
And her arm is a
Bandolier
Of crazy years
Some say She dissipates
Crazy 8&amp;rsquo;s
Oh no stay away
She has this mighty fine stack
Of powder
Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t want to be Her
But I know I know I&amp;rsquo;ll be on
On that porch soon
Kicking off my shoes.
She dances blind within</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speck</title>
      <link>/words/2011/speck/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/speck/</guid>
      <description>She descends In winged dominance Over barren waters My fear is entranced Holy reverberations Mountains quiver. High-winged creatures clap Distanced, they circle Her air. Time caves in my space She cups my broken waste. I am packed meat in Her crusted cocoon. I cry Her wasted tear. Blue sky above and near. Salted demons dance On thirsted tongue. And now, in Her rigid rock-womb A bloody song is rung. Ears bleed forth I’ve lost sight of Her sun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pour</title>
      <link>/words/2011/pour/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/pour/</guid>
      <description>Cousins of Dionysus Dance your might Around the centered pole Eerie delight The ground swallows your Magicians and sorcerers whole. The troubled elves gasp They laugh inside Back around and around Skip those feet Marching beat. The pole grows wider Your blood runs in cider. Human drama binds/runs the casting spell Dwelling gnomes Double-shaking shoulders Dusted tomes Thick ash smolders Grasping collective Threads of spiraling glee We dance with me. She prances heartache with them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out</title>
      <link>/words/2011/out/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/out/</guid>
      <description>And how you would just stir In that twilight haze That backlight painted my mind With soft expression Of your lost soul My hand would stare up at you Awaiting our first dance And I would lay back and watch you Fire your pyre around me And this place I somehow wonder if I will ever carry in that essence And if your story will ever find its break Our jagged spirits would just mesh As rusted gears I would stare at the ceiling And listen to your feet swim In ecstasy We were children of your tears </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bout</title>
      <link>/words/2011/bout/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/bout/</guid>
      <description>She dances in front of me. And I sing her praises. I watch her wail and tail. She is my goddess. She has fire and might. Completing sight. If you just see the way She breathes To me. And I in turn ignite Her forthright I’ve never seen a better dance I would never give this up No other swimmer in my cup I am the drummer to her pup Such plain expression Delightful children Spiritual premise DANCE CHILD!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slump</title>
      <link>/words/2011/slump/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/slump/</guid>
      <description>Sway sway The sands sprinkle Underneath Beige foothold arcing Rounded mounds Flowing sparks of joy Dissipating bliss breeds Grand visions The warrior arises from his Caged gluttony Gaia’s subtle song Whispering flesh In ear and mind bones A conduit of peaceful pairings Beneath these grains and above In one Encompassing Ray The warrior knows the dance To this song His feet yield The mighty blisters At Her Holy Command Sand kicks high Prepare the beast </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bright</title>
      <link>/words/2011/bright/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/bright/</guid>
      <description>Here I am Dancing in the wilderness. This secret is clutched in my grasps. I swing wildly with my right foot. I pound slightly with my left foot. They each sing the others’ praise. The dust swirls with such high regard. The long tail of wind directs beige perspective. A mound forms beneath, To the side, And on the top of its side, A cacophonoph approaches I find the right swings under me, The left swoops in front.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sun</title>
      <link>/words/2011/sun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/sun/</guid>
      <description>I want to see your thick Unapology. I want to see your best In me. Supple. Lying. In this dark bliss. The caverness. Of unyielding. Wastedness. Your eyes. In candlelight. Remind me. Of stricken gold light. And that bracelet. So unforetold. The glimmering diamond. Can I be so bold? I wish your Cadaver. Could be examined. Placed in abandon. To dance with. And holding tight. Abounding might. When you see me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wood</title>
      <link>/words/2011/wood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/wood/</guid>
      <description>When I walk her at 2AM. I feel at peace. In harmony. I resonate. When I walk her at 3AM. I am a paper sentinel. With a paper sword. When I walk her at 4AM. Her dew dresses my garment. I am at one. With this animal. We ride. I sing her discord. I wave her glee. And down her concrete stakes and wooden slabs. Along her many miles of pressed visions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharp</title>
      <link>/words/2011/sharp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/sharp/</guid>
      <description>When she closes her Mind’s eye She forgets her past. And everything. Caught in a twisted dream. I account for Her. It’s a broken mindset. But broken things Are meant to be fixed. Shifted asylum. Her heart is astray A wicked wonder. Hearing her voice again. Handshake left, and right. Are we in your crew? A crew of risk. Typing desk. Her eyes hold the sunlight Of a million moons. It’s a click on that door.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gloss</title>
      <link>/words/2011/gloss/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/gloss/</guid>
      <description>When I go into the depths of those Eyes It is like a mist And there’s this hum In my head.	There’s this brilliance. A dancing Sun. And I touch her skin. Just wanting to win. Somewhere in this Darkened Dance room. Her hips Roam with mine. Entwined. Dangerously. She tells me it’s a new day We’ll wait and see. She compliments me.	Heavily. A tear to my eye. I won’t deny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Float</title>
      <link>/words/2011/float/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/float/</guid>
      <description>You there! Little alien creature. Tell me what we’re here for. Hear for. And then. Maybe I’ll listen. Take a gander. Of your mission.	What you’re wishin’. Because, I am Like you.	Just spacin’ out.	Without a doubt. Trippin’. Wanderin’ Hopin’ we’re headin’	in the right. Direction. And when we don’t.	We don’t shout.	We don’t pout. We pontificate.	In your doubt. Wishin’ we were on that road. To nowhere. Something beautiful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Be</title>
      <link>/words/2011/be/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/be/</guid>
      <description>Truth be told Strangely Unique. She sleeps beneath my wings. Under this rock. Protectorate. Beneath my underworld. Gathering the impending storm. So dark.	So vivid. It gathers. Gathering. Like woodwork. I stare at it. Like it’s an image. Stolen from my soul. These beats in my head. I wonder where they storm from. Is it honest to steal their Meaning? Sometimes. I feel I Speak in Circles. So Let’s pick an angle And get this party Started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seem</title>
      <link>/words/2011/seem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/seem/</guid>
      <description>Her circles run coarse Around me. Coating me with Her Liquid cold fire I embrace Her Counted Shimmering blessings I pick Her favorite dance She follows. Leading Her into my circle. I pronounce Her Alive Ignited In Her ring Of flickering chaos. Wonder. I find Her bliss. She Smiles. Deep. One step too far. Never said. Never stated. She whispers selective patterns. I listen. But. The angle of my motioned feet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drop</title>
      <link>/words/2010/drop/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2010/drop/</guid>
      <description>She has Weltered walls. Shattering along Her weighted depth. Lighting dashes above. My shadow. Cascades. On Her metal Skin. I pull myself. Sword in hand. Up. Shattered. Wailing light. With careless effort, She Laughs at me. I push Up. She crashes around me. My rusted nails bite into her wasted root. I know I’m not the first. My own armored skin weighs me down. With great flair she brushes And shrugs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kid</title>
      <link>/words/2010/kid/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2010/kid/</guid>
      <description>tabletops
dusty spirals
threaded messages
dreary eyes
coupled passings
signed bread.
broken.
rememberance
violent
times
dark times
whisper
sweet tones
placated
curves
barren trigger
soiled snake
what time
jealousy
sacred vowels
coffee beans
solemn smiles
happy heartache
bloodshot whiskers
simple pain</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dumb</title>
      <link>/words/2010/dumb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2010/dumb/</guid>
      <description>She has this
stream of power
to her
cupping her cask
while muses dance.
twelve at a time.
drop a pair of dimes.
i only watch
and wait
what will she do
next.
spindled twilight
showered moonlight
casting rays of
soaked meat
coat of indifference
and i just watch
and wait
what will i do
next
with her.
templed city atop
that twisted hill.
bullies chase up
but don&amp;rsquo;t come down</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stir</title>
      <link>/words/2010/stir/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2010/stir/</guid>
      <description>You speak to me
In such soft
Visions.
Slowly
Forming
Spines
Splining from the light
Here. Within.
Fire in my eyes.
I know You’re here.
Storm in my ears.
Peace.
Sacred land.
I dance on You.
Screaming. Rapture.
Ashes burned on
The corners of my bones.
Embracing
Subtle wonders.
Placing sacrifice.
Enraging demons from
Afar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shaft</title>
      <link>/words/2010/shaft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2010/shaft/</guid>
      <description>Some wicked caves behind me.
Sifting.
Barren lakes.
Woodened souls.
Pour.
Shadows clatter.
Casting light.
On all of me.
And here now.
Gravel in knees.
At Her altar.
Ten points of light.
Skyward towards Her singing embrace.
She slowly tugs at the Acorn
From inside.
Peering.
Branches unfurling.
Leaves
Within, I feel Her.
Once again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Break</title>
      <link>/words/2009/break/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2009/break/</guid>
      <description>As you’re here. As I am. Once broken. Now I am. Broken Once. Broken Twice. Broken Narrow. Sacrifice. Once Sunday. Twice a Crowd. Here on Sunday. Break the Clouds. Your bread on Wednesday. Your blood is Mine. Sacrifice. Sacrifice. Here I stand on your Step. Make it Mine. Here I implore your Sacred vine. Some have sacred vows to store. Me, I have none to explore. Once Sunday. Once You. Once Sunday, Once you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some</title>
      <link>/words/2009/some/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2009/some/</guid>
      <description>Dionysus. Where is bliss? Capping on your head? Such a diss. Mommy and Daddy would be so proud. But you. Make us. SUFFER! Dionysus. Where’s your bliss? Tucked inside your barren mistress. Here I slay. From boot to tower. Struck by. Mother. Suckle away. Ungrateful wench. I see your cause. Unto. Unto. Present. In your eyes. I hear your waking eyes. In your voice. Across the room. Beacons me. </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
