<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brass on ossem: a creative space</title>
    <link>/boxes/brass/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Brass on ossem: a creative space</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/boxes/brass/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Whale</title>
      <link>/words/2011/whale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/whale/</guid>
      <description>A little refresher course for all you numerologists out there. Who’s to blame? All eyes on me. If you please. It’s a delegation.	Predilection. It’s a workshop. Post-mop. Operation. A post-mortem. A mirror on the wall. Watch those who are watching you. And you’ll see. It’s a sea. Of bluegrass. Simple glass. Brotherhood. Misunderstood. Malfunction. Sister break. Let’s watch these words we share. It’s imperative. We declare. Simpleton. Singleton. It might be whiskey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pounce</title>
      <link>/words/2011/pounce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/pounce/</guid>
      <description>She has these Starborne eyes. And I Here. on her blackened scarred beach. Face down. Spit the sand out my mouth. What happened? Where is she now? Standing over me. With that smile. And I wonder. What it meant. Don’t leave, Scorp. We need you. I. Need. You. II. Win this Holy Game. Under your covers. Left bare. The secret moment of your Life’s scare. I see your pattern. I know your fate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chirp</title>
      <link>/words/2010/chirp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2010/chirp/</guid>
      <description>Look at all this green.
Like a wall.
Like a fortress.
Boxed in.
So green.
So close.
And the chirps.
Chipper-chirper.
I count 5 birds.
2 here.
3 there.
This one over here stops when I walk this way.
This one over here stops when I listen too closely.
Like an old-skool hunter.
I read the Ether by chirp.
Now I sing with my new friends.
Mimic this one. I can do the tonality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some</title>
      <link>/words/2010/some/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2010/some/</guid>
      <description>She sort of is A Maenad The First. Dancing and talking On the Great Water Of life. And I, Well, I just watch. Scientifically. Artistically. Life-ly. I’m not sure what God she came from.	But she has my attention, now. For years now. And when she does dance. It’s to Her rhythm. I can’t help now But to keep her close. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bark</title>
      <link>/words/2009/bark/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2009/bark/</guid>
      <description>Certain kinda charm about her. Serendipity Lovely Glass Eye… On Her assheages Strands in the light Some sort of like wine..... Lonely sandwich On the floor Some crumbs. And a fire bird. hotter gets She Flaring greatness. Coupled sand. Packed pleasure. Beads of sound bounce around. Suppertime Draw the blinds. Hopeless love. Hopeless fissure. Crying. Breaking skyline In feast Calloused song </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peace</title>
      <link>/words/2008/peace/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2008/peace/</guid>
      <description>The Guides Circle in the gas The helium Propelled And circles Circling us In this spin. In this circle. They circle us. The guides. The gods guide the guides. Sun drips through. And these Guides. The voices. Hear them. Voices through the gas. Guides. Over and over. These guides hear us. Hear what they write. Circles and circles. Scribbles and scribbles. Years and years. They gain us. They gain it. Over and over the guides are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brand</title>
      <link>/words/2008/brand/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2008/brand/</guid>
      <description>As time passes Clouds cover the heat Rays of passion Stir and dance Form Breeds And I just rest Sifting These layers Grinding Passing Flight beckons Patience wears Something of a clock Cloak. Normal shadows Flight by And the sun That once was Echoes brilliantly Bonding Brotherhood And within deep Watered wells Lies my starry fate. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pick</title>
      <link>/words/2008/pick/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2008/pick/</guid>
      <description>She is. So. Perfectly. Sad. The drops. Of thunder. Pick. Brilliance. Apart. Her sadness. Her sadness. In me. Her sadness. Picks apart. In me. Tops of trees. In me. Tops of trees. In me. And with her tears. Breaks along. Her sadness. In me. Song of cheers. Elegance. Tears. Beautiful sadness. In me. In me. Beautiful sadness. Elegant madness. Wisdom dances. Around. Without. Counterpart. Tear apart. Trenches of tears. Cheeks and bleaks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curve</title>
      <link>/words/2008/curve/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2008/curve/</guid>
      <description>She dances along the rooftop of my mind. Blindly. And I, Blinded. Taste her. These feelings. She creates. Beats. Suddenly. Deeply. And when She looks down on me. From up there. I know. Confusion Is a friend. In times like these. Masked. Wrapped. Like a fire. Whereas. And she dances. Further along. My sacred plight. Wishes brew beside me. And this wooden stump. Nestled within my chin. Beckons. For her singing rain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creek</title>
      <link>/words/2008/creek/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2008/creek/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#39;s misty now. Outside. In here. Where there&amp;#39;s fear. Coating the lines of my Face. Bumping in the dark air. Sometimes. Light Finds its way. And I pass into the Flight of mind. Passing. Passing into my stare. They are memories now. And I wonder. Deeply. If what was meant to be. Passed into me. And here with mist in My hands. Rolling in my veins. These what once were. Passing into me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stare</title>
      <link>/stories/2007/stare/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2007/stare/</guid>
      <description>Still. Those eyes are what I&amp;rsquo;ll remember: piercing, intense. If anything it was if he was telling me something on a much different level than anything I had been accustomed to. I got the sense we were playing an intergalactic game of tag and he had just stuck it to me good, as if to say &amp;ldquo;gotcha, you lucky bastard. This time it&amp;rsquo;s your turn.&amp;rdquo; On a certain level I understood him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grease</title>
      <link>/words/2007/grease/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2007/grease/</guid>
      <description>Snoopin&amp;#39; around that fire. What are you doing there? --- &amp;#34;which twin was that?&amp;#34; From downtown… Nice shot! Well wouldn&amp;#39;t you know it, You weren&amp;#39;t so far off… Turns out…. … I was born a lefty… --- Here? That presence… Weird. Spectacular sirens. Ringing in her eyes. Someone special Has rung. Again. In my mind. Someone.New() Special clings to the underside of my Safehouse. And in the morning I hear her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ding</title>
      <link>/words/2006/ding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/ding/</guid>
      <description>Saturday night. Waiting. For her. Passive reproach. Someone’s watching. Stirring the sword. The air is sweet. Watching the beat of that drum. Doing nothing. Just being around. Doing. Nothing.	N1o2 t3h4h5i6n7g.8.9.0. Something Curious strikes a chord. That sounds mighty fine. Let’s examine that closer. Nocturnal nectar. Many rooms. Many locks. It’s interesting up here. Scary. Right now.	Not then. Now. Sweet sweet sw33t. What are you doing?	Finding did you do	something you seem	interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patch</title>
      <link>/words/2006/patch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/patch/</guid>
      <description>When our stars c o l l i d e Life is what it should be. Orbits surround us. Her Orbits surround me. Dance. Whimsical. Within. Me. Something in her air Strikes me true. Embracing I m a g I n a t I o n. Circling now … Something in here. Prickling. Stickling. Picking. Sight for a sore soul. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crisp</title>
      <link>/stories/2006/crisp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2006/crisp/</guid>
      <description>Still, the subtle scent of tobacco in the air snapped at the tip of Roger&amp;rsquo;s nose. It made him nervous somehow, but he managed to keep his composure. He could tell by the way his clothes were sticking to his body it had to have been about 4a.m. But you couldn&amp;rsquo;t tell that by the scenery around him. Life abounded. He wasn&amp;rsquo;t quite sure how he got here, or even which hotel he was in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stem</title>
      <link>/words/2006/stem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/stem/</guid>
      <description>Push goes the boundary. push push push. the boundary does go. and when you think it&amp;#39;s far enough push a little more to see where it goes. topple topple topple the towers don&amp;#39;t stand so much for dealing with foundation of sand. the weathered clouds are building a troubled tale that makes the troubled clouds are laughing I have disturbed their wake brewbrewbrew with naked dreams and broken seams they do amuse and abuse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coin</title>
      <link>/words/2006/coin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/coin/</guid>
      <description>take off your jeans show me what you got ok now put them back on before anyone sees. your secret&amp;#39;s safe with me. here in here. show me your regimen. sit-up si t- up you&amp;#39;re cute. I like that. someone should show you a good time. very g oo o o o oo o d oo oo o o might be fun. too? let me get your number haven&amp;#39;t got one in a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Race</title>
      <link>/stories/2006/race/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2006/race/</guid>
      <description>Harry couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but to reflect on what he just saw. He felt the need to shake his head a bit. It was as if a cobweb had enveloped his mind, causing him to shake and grind in a somewhat hurried discourse.
So Harry did hurry along his merry way. But still. What was it that he just saw? If he thought about it some more, would it change? Would he somehow begin to see his own mind and its own capacities in a different light?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>green</title>
      <link>/words/2006/green/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/green/</guid>
      <description>The sun sits bright where she lies telling story and story about her skies. those blue skies ? a soft sadness sad a soft madness mad somehow I see her sometimes traveling foot and hoof wander wander wonder happiness rains more than not when that sad voice rains on them don&amp;#39;t be troubled don&amp;#39;t be s u d d e n l y s u l l e n ly it all seems clear to the one you knew you wanted to the one you threw away not me of course but you or wait.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tea</title>
      <link>/words/2006/tea/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/tea/</guid>
      <description>Trouble is under those wings she never saw. even under those stars. those shadows carried higher sullen wants carried thoughts maybe she wanted those. treasured tossed. memories serrated. that was some foreign country yet vaguely familiar. the lights ahead so bright so light. so tight. I can just make them when I try. try try try. southern comforts no avail when you postulate your former sail. another troubled piece of a troubled puzzle ragged edges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crack</title>
      <link>/stories/2006/crack/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2006/crack/</guid>
      <description>Richard peered steadfastly into the sidewalk. It seemed barren somehow. As if a robber had broken in the middle of the night and swiped it of its character. The ridges speckled its plain face, smoothing in and out of a multitude of wrinkled pores.
A squint broke out over the ridge of Richard&amp;rsquo;s face. It was as if were dancing with a perplexing notion, waning in and out of tepid consciousness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That</title>
      <link>/words/2006/that/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/that/</guid>
      <description>that&amp;#39;s her hairtie in the stairwell in the stairwell of my mind do I pick it up? dust it off? or do i let it sit. trouble stirs with it deep inside. stir stir stir sometimes. it&amp;#39;s hard to let go. sometimes. it&amp;#39;s hard to be me. hanging on. with her. hanging on. with me. the past. is brittle. it seems? countenance wanes. please don&amp;#39;t wane. with me. trouble is where does she begin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speck</title>
      <link>/stories/2006/speck/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2006/speck/</guid>
      <description>With finality, the chair struck the bare wood floor. The air had no choice but to snap at first, but slowly it helped the chair down into oblivion. The weave of space and time undulated with a warm grace that offered a wishful eye and a careful stare of her newfound decision.
The creaking of the rope-spawn tendrils from high above tightened so sharply. Reverberations of past cries could only make their way into the current web of the room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slopes</title>
      <link>/stories/2006/slopes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2006/slopes/</guid>
      <description>As I got ready to leave to say my goodbyes, I noticed she got up to head upstairs before me. It was curious behavior, consistent with what I’ve seen from her all night. I made my round, hugging each person who had touched my life this clear misty morning. The subtle shadows of pine needles from the outside greens were starting to darken on the nearby windows. The sun was creeping into our consciousness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peak</title>
      <link>/words/2006/peak/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/peak/</guid>
      <description>troubled waters float this raft
from so long ago
sweetened stars from above
dance merrily below
her eyes, so beautiful
so glowing
mean everything to me
I reach for her countenance
to help balance these unbalanced
mountains in my mind
where she believed and others beamed
so callously behind
that smile
that smile
wondrous flare and charming aware
can only make me believe
I believe in her
I believe in us</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glow</title>
      <link>/stories/2006/glow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2006/glow/</guid>
      <description>Before I turned off the light to the room, I looked at the Buddha sitting on the shelf. He looked happy, as always; a certain vein of content flowed through the little statue. On this night I sort of related to the fellow. I sat there for a split second, captured and almost frozen, looking deep into his smile. A certain part of me saw myself in that chubby little cherub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pick</title>
      <link>/stories/2006/pick/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2006/pick/</guid>
      <description>I opened the door and was immediately confused on how I should feel. The little shop was more crowded than any time I had seen it. I could only guess the age group. Junior High? High school? I didn’t see any adults. A youth group, maybe?
The door closed behind me and I felt the old familiar rush of anxiety that I was the center of attention as everyone took a look at me to size me up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strap</title>
      <link>/stories/2006/strap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2006/strap/</guid>
      <description>The phone call was simple enough. She called to thank me. It was an innocent, innocuous moment, but something told me that I had just encountered a significant point in my life. It was almost as if I had passed a great moral test of some sort. I never met her, but here she was, thanking me in broken English. “Thank you, Greg. Thank you.”
It was almost as if life itself, in some sort of twisted incarnation, was telling me something pivotal – something meaningful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hail</title>
      <link>/stories/2005/hail/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2005/hail/</guid>
      <description>And there, walking along side of the parking building, Roger knew he was about to taste destiny.
Roger was on his way to pick up some friends for the night out. They lived in a busy part of downtown. People lined the streets one either side, causing traffic to snarl its way throughout. Roger had just parked his car in the parking structure to the right of him and was on his way to his friends’ apartment two blocks south.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Way</title>
      <link>/words/2005/way/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/way/</guid>
      <description>and there, skin to skin our destinies pinned and there, traveled sadness residual quickness and there, something familiar stirs within us and there, something plain weaves throughout us and there, souls connect barren contact and there, I feel you read me you’ll never finish me and there, something amiss sudden, sullen abyss and here, once dancing in doubt I have finally figured you out </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sink</title>
      <link>/words/2005/sink/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/sink/</guid>
      <description>Troubled seas in those dreams
Of hers.
And I see them. So alive
In me.
Harrowed response.
Sloppy sour.
She floats. I see it.
She drifts. I feel it.
That smile is so cracked and
Twisted.
Only soft memories fly with me.
Hallowed sunlight.
Take flight
With her.
Must I once again
Drown in her waters.
Scorpio passing
Gemini drowning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ray</title>
      <link>/stories/2005/ray/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2005/ray/</guid>
      <description>And there, exiting that bustling restaurant, Ray felt a certain sense deep within that he hadn’t felt for some time. In a way, he felt that he had been shifted in some way, some way deep inside.
His friends were well on their way to their cars, but Ray couldn’t help but to wonder if they themselves were touched in the same manner he was. It was as if their conversation had impacted him in a way that will be with him for the rest of his life, perhaps in the final days of death, when all who surround him are nameless unrecognizable creatures of care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jon</title>
      <link>/stories/2005/jon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2005/jon/</guid>
      <description>And when Jon finished wiping the mirror with that dampened hand-towel of his, he felt that somehow his life had changed. Something deep within that mirror struck back at him. There wasn’t a familiar reflection that lived within the mirror this morning. No, this morning Jon saw the very thing that looked back at him. He couldn’t help but to look back. It called into him to stare it in the eyes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tone</title>
      <link>/words/2005/tone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/tone/</guid>
      <description>suffered neuron amount of wake troubled luring a given take passing virgo mind aware having witnessed given flare outside tremors house arrest inside horrors lemming’s test circling crows fret fret fret boughs brought low a coward set shaking towers mindful light kindling sour masking chide backlit hair sundown ghost moonlight share harried most haggard notions tired sake midnight nations sacred take </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>George</title>
      <link>/stories/2005/george/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2005/george/</guid>
      <description>And it was there with those eyes that George knew he made his mistake. Looking around with all these strangers, he could only grasp his memory by mere threads. How did he get here? Where were his friends? Where was he?
So many people bristled at his presence in that old rusted house, the muffled music made him confused on whether he should be happy or sad. People stopped briefly in the hallway to dispense somewhat honest conversations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step</title>
      <link>/words/2005/step/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/step/</guid>
      <description>hollowed shining ringing her echoes she refines that which is there forever entwined and enwrapped and furrowed and programmed within the great divide until we know how long it is with the other side, I won’t know and that sort of scares the essence of spirited debate and heart and how can that know if I don’t know the essence of me. search and search and search I may wander aimlessly are you ok with that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wide</title>
      <link>/words/2005/wide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/wide/</guid>
      <description>hands reached out the blue dances blindly around my fingertips around her. around us. I see her shining through through closed eyes. she smiles so peacefully on my bliss. traveling from fields of wandering green we hold each other forever. forever. the wind smiles on us too together we were meant to be. together with that harmony. this is some dance. she follows my lead. I know that this is where we are meant to be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Murk</title>
      <link>/words/2005/murk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/murk/</guid>
      <description>there’s wild water in that brown-eyed whirlwind I must confess, if it were any differently I would rescind. my sails will snag upon her force but I know it won’t take me far. for I have only traveled these waters mapped by other stars. troubled waters in a different time troubled waters these will be mine she’ll dash me further than I’ve been before. she’ll throw me further than my plans in store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Link</title>
      <link>/words/2005/link/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/link/</guid>
      <description>the look in her eye makes me wonder if her story is deep within me traveling vast levels spiraling down my spine that smile so weak trembling off that corner haunting past must be it don’t unlock it makes it worse climb that mountain now that’s an adventure ah, her trials so innocent and i’m so guilty that look of hers is the look of mine </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Try</title>
      <link>/words/2005/try/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/try/</guid>
      <description>look in my eyes tell me how much you hate this game as you make your next move as you try to beat me chilling visions in our minds I see you before you think you see me dancing together unity prosperity illusions our reflections on bathroom floors your skin. our game is perfect don’t lie to me please. don’t stop lying to me </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beams</title>
      <link>/words/2005/beams/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/beams/</guid>
      <description>what I miss most of all are those times in that underbrush with you those rocks. that September mist together under that sunlight playing with those autumn leaves it was there that I found god in your wake I felt your heat against mine For the first time beautiful things beautiful you our hands so young and pure that sweater of yours that’s right I cut my foot that one time, didn’t i?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mold</title>
      <link>/words/2005/mold/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/mold/</guid>
      <description>stroke of impatience stroke of genius I am finally settling into the person you crafted me with great care and jealousy great precision ////settling//into//you///// ////settling//into//you///// that’s what you want isn’t it? puzzle pieces fill me and that’s all they are these creases in my smile lined by the jigsaw not a star not a sky trailing in your delight I envy that smile smile more prickly sensations behind my eyes so true so blue to be like you so not me but the me you want me to be </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temp</title>
      <link>/words/2005/temp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/temp/</guid>
      <description>it’s crazy outside and she’s in here with me crazy in here too. wandering in that forest once again. paths in hundreds of directions of paths the trees dream of me anything to be their hero her smile seems so far away from the likes of me bathing in tragedy I am rife with brooding tendrils </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Won</title>
      <link>/words/2005/won/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/won/</guid>
      <description>reach out to me you’ll see you’ll see forest in daylight I’ll be there do you care? won’t you share? why don’t you call me sounds kinda cool doesn’t it together we’ll go out see what it’s about reaching. I see that hand. oh there it is again. quite the stretch is there a reason for the riddle? oh it’s your riddle I should have known. it’s a tricky one, I see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plank</title>
      <link>/words/2005/plank/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/plank/</guid>
      <description>one by one she pops the stars in my eyes in the needle goes slowly through my brown skies a prick a stick wincing yet grinning she twists that needle so true and straight watching me squirm without much debate I kick and yell and beg for more I yearn to know what she has in store I barter for her pain like a fool taking me to her school excrement in her stool I smell like a fat fool with a little drool spin that metal how I jerk in glee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grain</title>
      <link>/words/2005/grain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/grain/</guid>
      <description>my wrinkled shriveled carcass washes up
against her salty sand.
seeping into my cuts and sores,
her jagged rocks
rip and stretch my haggard meat.
and cut against my chipping bones.
on her sea of grains, crabs claw at my fingernails
they pull and tug until i snap with satisfaction.
birds,
once singing with our great harmony
now pick at my eyes with
infected beaks.
they clip the whites of my eyes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miss</title>
      <link>/words/2005/miss/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/miss/</guid>
      <description>fettered quickly upon her barren shores I know what’s best for her and her smile sinking quickly beneath me. she sings a song I do not know or have never heard. what’s to know about her? about us? fine day for a matinee. I say. surely in the quick of dawn. we are one chances are we. chances are we. chances are we. who said we never owe a creature&amp;#39;s stow perchance it’s happenstance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Say</title>
      <link>/words/2005/say/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/say/</guid>
      <description>how do I show her
the light in my sky?
without showing her</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wick</title>
      <link>/words/2005/wick/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/wick/</guid>
      <description>release that grass into your minions patience is a virtue. your virtue. not mine. making sense yet? in a multitude of perfection. quite the tower you have here. showered yet? trouble lurks underwater, I understand. no, I don’t. stretch into the mindscape of your sandscape.that’snotaword. i hear you, but don’t want to. aren’t you gone yet? shake that web server just a little more stop wearing my underwear. question that chimpmonk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wind</title>
      <link>/words/2005/wind/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/wind/</guid>
      <description>Step into my sling. if you dare. For it’s a fun ride to ride. for a while. I admit. Maybe you should try? Just once? On you hop and Around and round we go. A blur it becomes. A flurry it yields. Where it stops. Only I know. For you’re in my sling. My witty ride. My complex side. Slide and twist. Isn’t this fun? Squirm and yell. Are you done?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
