<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2013 on ossem: a creative space</title>
    <link>/year/2013/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2013 on ossem: a creative space</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/year/2013/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Trust</title>
      <link>/words/2013/trust/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/trust/</guid>
      <description>When She cries in me. (I am insane). And the words we make. (are just a game). How does one go mad? (sure you’re not glad?) Is it a suit and bow tie? (don’t forget to die). How do I channel you? (you’re still living). How do I level you? (you’re still breathing). These words we use. (are just a game). Mystery tells. (another story). A space to His own. (it’s His kingdom, after all).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tramp</title>
      <link>/words/2013/tramp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/tramp/</guid>
      <description>A god, Broken into billions of pieces. A piece is you. To gather the pieces is… a clue. Are you a piece of me? Am I a piece of you? How do I see this piece of me? Where? Shattered. Assembled whole. Ocean images. You must show something for your efforts. Something. There are trysts in these parts. There are trusts, too. I have the karma divide. She is not very nice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pure</title>
      <link>/words/2013/pure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/pure/</guid>
      <description>Thoughts and dreams… and mystery. She sings to me With Such Broken Promises. I cling to Her twisted stains. For my life. (in disbelief) In terror, I am Her puppet. In life, I am Her master. In troubled keep. I dance Her wake. I wrap myself in Her mistakes. For Her misery is my desire. A steadfast plan of mire. And desolate beauty. Seen. Lost in Her seams. I long for Her lonely glance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tempt</title>
      <link>/words/2013/tempt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/tempt/</guid>
      <description>I is the drink. Do I get paid to think? Cummervescence. Pleasance. Trysto. Manifesto. Where is the mindset? Where is the bodytet? No Pain. No Fear. Play your hand. It’s in the sand. What’s air to you? Just asking. Air is nice. It’s not ice. My crazy little friend. Chipzah. To me, it means prosperity. See, I dance around. Unexpopound(ed). And when the moon’s not right. We solicify it. Same ol’ me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep</title>
      <link>/photos/deep/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photos/deep/</guid>
      <description>Burning my copy of Garbage and the Goddess, as instructed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Try</title>
      <link>/words/2013/try/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/try/</guid>
      <description>She lights my world. In me. And i. am. Hers. I echo through Her landscape. Her sounds bound in bliss. Lighted by fire. Seething The Bright. I slide down Her magnificent high. And then She becomes me. The absurdity. I reign Her chaos so suddenly. We grasp upon the signs of dance. I am drowned in Her expanse. We celebrate the Godspace. Broken like bread on a tree’s face. She whispers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thing</title>
      <link>/words/2013/thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/thing/</guid>
      <description>A lover’s space, A hint of the unthinkable. A chord of trust. A messenger in God’s space. A forsaken plan. A song of pain. A coward’s trace, A trace of the predictable, A patio’s preface. A repetitive apology. A muse speaks. A maze breaks. A dance turns to words. A word turns to God. A riddle becomes God. A solution begins, A friendship trends, A team mends. A cycle of truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tea</title>
      <link>/words/2013/tea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/tea/</guid>
      <description>In my state. Counting. 0000000000000. T-state? Is this an edge push or not? An edgue –push state? (Demonstration?) A pish. A puwsh. A blinding. Push spiy. Spoy.. Qqqqqq believing., And onccccccce a;; beliving is done. A student of crime. Now, that’s the first thing that’s mmade sense…. Thru. These broken deade keyboards, The then sealed. Your eyes. Open.d. Miracle. Whart. Is the message. Pretenser. Pretenser? What is the mesaage? Q	whqat is your messsaagwe?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stand</title>
      <link>/words/2013/stand/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/stand/</guid>
      <description>She’s got a dirty eye Placed in me She’s got a filthy spirit Dancing A dirty eye Not far from peace A filthy spirit Pleasing A time comes Wrapped in strands Of stars And rapture Her voice Here Her space Vision Entering upon the Sun Joining my broken body Pieces and dust Mixed destiny Stirred vastness I am Her wasted soldier Sword in broken hand I tremble Fortified She seals me Forged in night She takes me Shadows breaking sand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Short</title>
      <link>/words/2013/short/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/short/</guid>
      <description>Are you crying? Are you dead? Order. Prestigue. sAfter all that… Yoiur at a hakter, Is nthere an aex”? Your study yoouuuur ahit/. Youuuuve been preshifted. Is that goofd? You habve n o understanding. Ill dance to me. T m humanity.\ \\	\	\\\	\\ Well. It’s us;. You’re such a chhhhhhhhhhhhheater. Flesh. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dirt</title>
      <link>/words/2013/dirt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/dirt/</guid>
      <description>Strike a dime’s eye. It’s your might. Are we children? Or are we dancers? A child dances upon leaves. Who are we? Figure it out. A cold doubt. We are the Kings and Queens of Mystery Eternal. A golden sun upon yourself. Am I you? Am I him? (frame). Deny the God upon your servant’s brow. In your head are we? Then what are we here for? I fold my eyelid over itself.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
