<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2012 on ossem: a creative space</title>
    <link>/year/2012/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2012 on ossem: a creative space</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/year/2012/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rock</title>
      <link>/photos/rock/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photos/rock/</guid>
      <description>Page 87 of Garbage and the Goddess. What struck me about this image was the overwhelmingly male energy presented in the foreground of this photo with a powerful-looking female in the background, somehow keeping everyone in check. I sketched my own variation of this photo here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rock</title>
      <link>/sketches/rock/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sketches/rock/</guid>
      <description>My interpretation of page 87 from Garbage and the Goddess. In the background hangs The Great Wave of Kanagawa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Link</title>
      <link>/words/2012/link/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/link/</guid>
      <description>And here. We are beautifully broken. So perfectly lost. How did we get here? So fairytale. A lost ship has sunk. From its coast, it dares not tell. Angels swoop upon the treasure. (it is their pleasure) Collect the gold. It’s greed, after all. Timeless classic. Pace a time’s forth. (are you in love again?) There is something to be bought. A price that is sought. There are stories to be won.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bring</title>
      <link>/words/2012/bring/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/bring/</guid>
      <description>And fell, the hammer did fell. The pressure, misfit. Hey, did you just make that? It’s my art, so yes. Side room. Is this side room ours? ? Wow. You stretched it. (hard). Why won’t you hit your heart? A dance of pleasure. Aced of bacon. A slide show. Prescence. Hey,. That’s wrong. Cornerstone is set. Hm, Milk and gasoline. (set us free). Where’s the pleasure principle? TELL ME! The guided crosses will know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ask</title>
      <link>/words/2012/ask/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/ask/</guid>
      <description>It’s a dead end rodeo. Which way will you go. I choose peace. I choose mayhem. That’s funny. That’s not where you were Seconds ago. Tell you what. (we’ll flip a coin). Flip One. (here it goes). Flip two (here’s his campaign manager). Flip three. (here’s to you and me). Get that out of your system? Grind and mind, actually. I’m sure. OK? A protective bith slap… Is he,… watching his language?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Line</title>
      <link>/words/2012/line/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/line/</guid>
      <description>Well, I&amp;rsquo;ve got
The world in my eyes and
The Universe in my Heart
I&amp;rsquo;m not sure where to start
Maybe with you.
We&amp;rsquo;ll ride the blue
Break the clear
Ride the clear
Run the fear
Be the fear
In your presence
The choice is clear
I&amp;rsquo;m your terrorist
I&amp;rsquo;m your hero
I&amp;rsquo;m the everything
You don&amp;rsquo;t know
I&amp;rsquo;m the terrorist
I&amp;rsquo;m the hero
There&amp;rsquo;s no telling
The seed I sow</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set</title>
      <link>/words/2012/set/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/set/</guid>
      <description>The Sun sets, yet,
The World in Her Eyes
The Wings of Her Flight
The Sun sets, yet.
The Sun sets, yet,
The dare to change
The Air of Change
The Sun sets, yet.
The Sun sets, yet,
The nation of sorrow
The heart of tomorrow
The Sun sets, yet.
The Sun sets, yet,
The happiness within Her
The peace beneath Her.
The Sun sets, yet.
The Sun sets, yet,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Be</title>
      <link>/words/2012/be/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/be/</guid>
      <description>How do you dissolve nerousis? With a toothpick. Now, dance with me. I ain’t hitting that with a glass case. Now a vase. Heyyy! Get it! (alignment) Just being honest. Now, back to that honesty. Does it cost you? There’s a price, isn’t there? Watch the table. TH e table is ours. What do you see? A beautiful song. So not right. What do you hear? An anthem. Now we’re rockin’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tame</title>
      <link>/words/2012/tame/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/tame/</guid>
      <description>In my dreams
I am tucked in Her sleep.
Awakened. Silenced.
In Her fears
She is brought to silenced knee.
A knee to here?
So far from me.
Wet. The streets are soaked.
And the drain is dazed.
Honeyphazed.
A prerecording.
A sonboarding.
A boundary.
A dance space.
In this place, a secret message.
In this family, a tone is set.
Dry rock.
You mean an ice cold precipice
Rock solid can challenge the rights up here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cave</title>
      <link>/words/2012/cave/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/cave/</guid>
      <description>Your brain is hot. Ot’s thinking. A pressure monet. A pressure taking. Is this your wallet. Is this your monhey. Hahaha… I disagree. Who is that guy anyways? Well, I’ll tell you a story. Blah blah, Should you disrupt that one. Thos one. Well politics. Politics are fun. Now, where did the humor go? My humor? Your humour? The humor is here. You watched him as a necessary element. Let me place this base.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trim</title>
      <link>/words/2012/trim/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/trim/</guid>
      <description>Heated dance. Billowing hair. Her look. In my locked cell. She gives me grace. Spaced shoulders. Pumping… This is her crowd. By the hand, She takes me. I feel her sweat. Her heat takes me. Jumping, Her look. unfolds my world. And the way she is Makes me wonder what will be. Supple responsibility. In here. We are partners. Assembled whole. A problem is just a label. We see the stage for what it is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chain</title>
      <link>/words/2012/chain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/chain/</guid>
      <description>Chained.
Behind blacked walls.
A screen appears.
She appears to me.
Human form.
Speaking. On authority.
And now, the quest begins.
An innerspace of wills.
To read the ether.
To provide the circumstance.
The mist dissolves in sunlight.
Tremendous bright.
Her energy radiates beauty.
Dissipating lock and key.
And here. In our time.
We play the tones of life.’
And wonder the keys and charms within.
Can I make this better?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sense</title>
      <link>/words/2012/sense/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/sense/</guid>
      <description>Well, she’s a righteous shortcoming I want to be her. To dance her. To lick her skin deep within She knows my heartache (It’s a sick mistake.) I can’t break her trust I must trip in her eyes It’s no surprise Her heart tries to capture That what is in me When I soak in the ripples of her bliss I cannot dismiss that I No longer No longer No longer Know me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perch</title>
      <link>/words/2012/perch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/perch/</guid>
      <description>She breaks upon Her
Perch, timeless.
We are the golden gods
Of a silenced age.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rhyme</title>
      <link>/words/2012/rhyme/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/rhyme/</guid>
      <description>I gauged her thighs carefully. Broken skirt. Her paw had summit. I fathomed a conversation. But instead I settled into Her. Gauging again. I watch her thighs. She sees my moves. I reangle. WAY overcompensate. She flees. At the sight of me. Hands clawing. Turn right. Into left. Mirror passes pillar. She peeks past plastic star. Am I too far? Too distant? I drive. Not too fast. Not too slow. But there’s a jacket on the car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beach</title>
      <link>/words/2012/beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/beach/</guid>
      <description>Chipper chapper. Let’s stop this right here. Isn’t this the same as the last? Twelve hours at a time is a long time To read minds. Isn’t it nice to be around people again? To what end? What’s your purpose. To me, Everyone Is poetry. Dancing energy. Your spirit is captured in me. You’re keeping note of names, I like that. Letters, spelling. A nice chat. On a sunny afternoon. The 10:10 would appreciate that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Same</title>
      <link>/words/2012/same/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/same/</guid>
      <description>That was my card. That was our card. She flipped it on its face. I knew it before we grabbed it. The hobbit post-faced it. Row of ladies on the left. Row of guys on the right. Fat bastard’s in my chair The queen’s gotta pair. It’s time to go. It’s time to row. 9:07PM specifically. The trees are leaves. Our eyes met. Consistently. An eye-five. Pleased me. She asked my name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fine</title>
      <link>/words/2012/fine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/fine/</guid>
      <description>When she smiles They, smile. It makes me wonder why I feel this way. And all the connections, and emotions. To deal with them. In your way. And my way. There are very bad things in this world. Very good things, too. Which ones do you choose? We continue to choose both. Imbalance would be treason. If “they” know everything about you, What is there to fear? To be ashamed? To be guilty of?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live</title>
      <link>/words/2012/live/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/live/</guid>
      <description>Stand
Marching band
Witches bring us</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gut</title>
      <link>/words/2012/gut/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/gut/</guid>
      <description>Answer the question, Claire. There’s an act in all of us. So then, you’re not a … What was the question again? That’s funny, I forgot the question as well. So what are we doing here? Seeking truth. I’m seeking destruction. Hot. Cold. Up. Down. Left Right White Black Peace Trouble Treble Bass Spirit Soul Light Sound Science Art Life Religion Normalcy Anxiety Honesty Trixstery Light Shadow Flattery Stealing Child Adult Adult Child Correcting Cheating Principle Law Good Great Slow Fast Self Phenomena </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modes</title>
      <link>/words/2012/modes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/modes/</guid>
      <description>Sleepy eye
Angry shaman
Wry guy
Creating</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love</title>
      <link>/words/2012/love/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/love/</guid>
      <description>Death. Life. Is that your wife?
Soldiers understand the meanings.
Just don&amp;rsquo;t think of these while sleeping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I</title>
      <link>/words/2012/i/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/i/</guid>
      <description>I’ll step into your garden While following my bliss. Bliss, while misunderstood, is just a property of your path. It’s a compensation of thinking. That is: feeling. Back to your garden: There is a circle. There are two trees. Twins, I’d say. And then there’s this creepy shed. The leaves paint a path outside of the circle. All the while, I keep my eye steady for the people that might approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tip</title>
      <link>/words/2012/tip/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/tip/</guid>
      <description>Levitating drink off the side bar.
I thought you were smart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mine</title>
      <link>/words/2012/mine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/mine/</guid>
      <description>It is not good for man to be alone
So when man begins to dance again
The steps placed square within him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prime</title>
      <link>/words/2012/prime/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/prime/</guid>
      <description>enter right
Through the left.
Your frame still
Manifests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let</title>
      <link>/words/2012/let/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/let/</guid>
      <description>How do I live up to this? Looking to the side stage. My Stage. You caught it, you bought it. I’m flipping caps here. I don’t think I can dance this stepfloor. … and then… “I’m sort of interested in honesty.” Ya, what is honesty, anyways? Honesty is reaching for the wrong bottle. And knowing it. Honesty is predicting the future. Then facing it. Honesty is consistency. Didn’t you say that consistency is key?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lick</title>
      <link>/words/2012/lick/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/lick/</guid>
      <description>Fire up your gods.
R
A valued goddess
Has stories in her chest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sell</title>
      <link>/words/2012/sell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/sell/</guid>
      <description>What are your signs? Would I invite Her to church? There’s a roundwheel going around here. Flow the spigot. The spigot is good. Spigggots are also nice, as well. ARE WE IN HELL??? A flower will suit you well. But next time, the flower is there. Not here. All of these multitudes of possibilities. Your area is weak. Where are these starstruck adventures as youth? UNCOMPROMISING, SIR???\ Well, philosophy is one thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gift</title>
      <link>/words/2012/gift/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/gift/</guid>
      <description>The cars sound empty And hollow. The band swings mighty hallowed. We walk with saints. She’s the lead singer. Man she can belt a tune. And there’s the story teller. Telling your fortunes. A roving band. Walking the streets of netherland. Strange talent of gods. Speak with us. Calling / sparking / presence. Man, let’s load up on the spirits. Poets of concrete. No longer discrete. Where did you get that shirt?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
