<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2006 on ossem: a creative space</title>
    <link>/year/2006/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2006 on ossem: a creative space</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2006 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/year/2006/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Shy</title>
      <link>/words/2006/shy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/shy/</guid>
      <description>(an)	Ha ha. Not so obvious… Hot white Starlight She doesn’t blink seem Hm.	To me. Trouble is	let’s talk a while. Trouble does. Somewhere in pull up a chair	Here.	pull your hair This pasture.	Her eyes are… Did she just say that?	What is this that I just found myself in… Seems dark And bright At the same time.	Well that was that. It is what it is. Telltale mysteries come to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ding</title>
      <link>/words/2006/ding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/ding/</guid>
      <description>Saturday night. Waiting. For her. Passive reproach. Someone’s watching. Stirring the sword. The air is sweet. Watching the beat of that drum. Doing nothing. Just being around. Doing. Nothing.	N1o2 t3h4h5i6n7g.8.9.0. Something Curious strikes a chord. That sounds mighty fine. Let’s examine that closer. Nocturnal nectar. Many rooms. Many locks. It’s interesting up here. Scary. Right now.	Not then. Now. Sweet sweet sw33t. What are you doing?	Finding did you do	something you seem	interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mean</title>
      <link>/words/2006/mean/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/mean/</guid>
      <description>Snap Pop Pop Snapple Something broke Inside of her Something hooked Whoa. Me me me. He He He. e e e Lettuce play. Verbage Of Nothing. Nothing is something. That&amp;#39;s the best I got. Suffered within that s t a t e o f m I n d State of mine. Mine mine mine. That&amp;#39;s when she smiles. And I crack. Under that bridge of ours. Can I borrow a dollar?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patch</title>
      <link>/words/2006/patch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/patch/</guid>
      <description>When our stars c o l l i d e Life is what it should be. Orbits surround us. Her Orbits surround me. Dance. Whimsical. Within. Me. Something in her air Strikes me true. Embracing I m a g I n a t I o n. Circling now … Something in here. Prickling. Stickling. Picking. Sight for a sore soul.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stem</title>
      <link>/words/2006/stem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/stem/</guid>
      <description>Push goes the boundary. push push push. the boundary does go. and when you think it&amp;#39;s far enough push a little more to see where it goes. topple topple topple the towers don&amp;#39;t stand so much for dealing with foundation of sand. the weathered clouds are building a troubled tale that makes the troubled clouds are laughing I have disturbed their wake brewbrewbrew with naked dreams and broken seams they do amuse and abuse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coin</title>
      <link>/words/2006/coin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/coin/</guid>
      <description>take off your jeans show me what you got ok now put them back on before anyone sees. your secret&amp;#39;s safe with me. here in here. show me your regimen. sit-up si t- up you&amp;#39;re cute. I like that. someone should show you a good time. very g oo o o o oo o d oo oo o o might be fun. too? let me get your number haven&amp;#39;t got one in a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prick</title>
      <link>/words/2006/prick/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/prick/</guid>
      <description>the twins are talking to the scales again as you see and read the time has come to explore some more. whether you are on b o a r d o1r n2o3t. quiver.sliver.river. thistimethistimethistime. silver? more on board this time. there is more balance this time. I have learned. this time. sometimes riddles abound and riddles abound in me the sorcerer&amp;#39;s sword rests in willowed wake. across the pond in the seas a quest it does make.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Race</title>
      <link>/stories/2006/race/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2006/race/</guid>
      <description>Harry couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but to reflect on what he just saw. He felt the need to shake his head a bit. It was as if a cobweb had enveloped his mind, causing him to shake and grind in a somewhat hurried discourse.
So Harry did hurry along his merry way. But still. What was it that he just saw? If he thought about it some more, would it change? Would he somehow begin to see his own mind and its own capacities in a different light?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>green</title>
      <link>/words/2006/green/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/green/</guid>
      <description>The sun sits bright where she lies telling story and story about her skies. those blue skies ? a soft sadness sad a soft madness mad somehow I see her sometimes traveling foot and hoof wander wander wonder happiness rains more than not when that sad voice rains on them don&amp;#39;t be troubled don&amp;#39;t be s u d d e n l y s u l l e n ly it all seems clear to the one you knew you wanted to the one you threw away not me of course but you or wait.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tea</title>
      <link>/words/2006/tea/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/tea/</guid>
      <description>Trouble is under those wings she never saw. even under those stars. those shadows carried higher sullen wants carried thoughts maybe she wanted those. treasured tossed. memories serrated. that was some foreign country yet vaguely familiar. the lights ahead so bright so light. so tight. I can just make them when I try. try try try. southern comforts no avail when you postulate your former sail. another troubled piece of a troubled puzzle ragged edges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crack</title>
      <link>/stories/2006/crack/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2006/crack/</guid>
      <description>Richard peered steadfastly into the sidewalk. It seemed barren somehow. As if a robber had broken in the middle of the night and swiped it of its character. The ridges speckled its plain face, smoothing in and out of a multitude of wrinkled pores.
A squint broke out over the ridge of Richard&amp;rsquo;s face. It was as if were dancing with a perplexing notion, waning in and out of tepid consciousness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That</title>
      <link>/words/2006/that/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/that/</guid>
      <description>that&amp;#39;s her hairtie in the stairwell in the stairwell of my mind do I pick it up? dust it off? or do i let it sit. trouble stirs with it deep inside. stir stir stir sometimes. it&amp;#39;s hard to let go. sometimes. it&amp;#39;s hard to be me. hanging on. with her. hanging on. with me. the past. is brittle. it seems? countenance wanes. please don&amp;#39;t wane. with me. trouble is where does she begin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speck</title>
      <link>/stories/2006/speck/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2006/speck/</guid>
      <description>With finality, the chair struck the bare wood floor. The air had no choice but to snap at first, but slowly it helped the chair down into oblivion. The weave of space and time undulated with a warm grace that offered a wishful eye and a careful stare of her newfound decision.
The creaking of the rope-spawn tendrils from high above tightened so sharply. Reverberations of past cries could only make their way into the current web of the room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slopes</title>
      <link>/stories/2006/slopes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2006/slopes/</guid>
      <description>As I got ready to leave to say my goodbyes, I noticed she got up to head upstairs before me. It was curious behavior, consistent with what I’ve seen from her all night. I made my round, hugging each person who had touched my life this clear misty morning. The subtle shadows of pine needles from the outside greens were starting to darken on the nearby windows. The sun was creeping into our consciousness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peak</title>
      <link>/words/2006/peak/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/peak/</guid>
      <description>troubled waters float this raft
from so long ago
sweetened stars from above
dance merrily below
her eyes, so beautiful
so glowing
mean everything to me
I reach for her countenance
to help balance these unbalanced
mountains in my mind
where she believed and others beamed
so callously behind
that smile
that smile
wondrous flare and charming aware
can only make me believe
I believe in her
I believe in us</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glow</title>
      <link>/stories/2006/glow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2006/glow/</guid>
      <description>Before I turned off the light to the room, I looked at the Buddha sitting on the shelf. He looked happy, as always; a certain vein of content flowed through the little statue. On this night I sort of related to the fellow. I sat there for a split second, captured and almost frozen, looking deep into his smile. A certain part of me saw myself in that chubby little cherub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pick</title>
      <link>/stories/2006/pick/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2006/pick/</guid>
      <description>I opened the door and was immediately confused on how I should feel. The little shop was more crowded than any time I had seen it. I could only guess the age group. Junior High? High school? I didn’t see any adults. A youth group, maybe?
The door closed behind me and I felt the old familiar rush of anxiety that I was the center of attention as everyone took a look at me to size me up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strap</title>
      <link>/stories/2006/strap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2006/strap/</guid>
      <description>The phone call was simple enough. She called to thank me. It was an innocent, innocuous moment, but something told me that I had just encountered a significant point in my life. It was almost as if I had passed a great moral test of some sort. I never met her, but here she was, thanking me in broken English. “Thank you, Greg. Thank you.”
It was almost as if life itself, in some sort of twisted incarnation, was telling me something pivotal – something meaningful.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>