<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2009 on ossem: a creative space</title>
    <link>/year/2009/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2009 on ossem: a creative space</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/year/2009/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Break</title>
      <link>/words/2009/break/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2009/break/</guid>
      <description>As you’re here. As I am. Once broken. Now I am. Broken Once. Broken Twice. Broken Narrow. Sacrifice. Once Sunday. Twice a Crowd. Here on Sunday. Break the Clouds. Your bread on Wednesday. Your blood is Mine. Sacrifice. Sacrifice. Here I stand on your Step. Make it Mine. Here I implore your Sacred vine. Some have sacred vows to store. Me, I have none to explore. Once Sunday. Once You. Once Sunday, Once you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some</title>
      <link>/words/2009/some/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2009/some/</guid>
      <description>Dionysus. Where is bliss? Capping on your head? Such a diss. Mommy and Daddy would be so proud. But you. Make us. SUFFER! Dionysus. Where’s your bliss? Tucked inside your barren mistress. Here I slay. From boot to tower. Struck by. Mother. Suckle away. Ungrateful wench. I see your cause. Unto. Unto. Present. In your eyes. I hear your waking eyes. In your voice. Across the room. Beacons me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bark</title>
      <link>/words/2009/bark/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2009/bark/</guid>
      <description>Certain kinda charm about her. Serendipity Lovely Glass Eye… On Her assheages Strands in the light Some sort of like wine..... Lonely sandwich On the floor Some crumbs. And a fire bird. hotter gets She Flaring greatness. Coupled sand. Packed pleasure. Beads of sound bounce around. Suppertime Draw the blinds. Hopeless love. Hopeless fissure. Crying. Breaking skyline In feast Calloused song</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>