<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tin on ossem: a creative space</title>
    <link>/boxes/tin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tin on ossem: a creative space</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/boxes/tin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pi</title>
      <link>/sketches/pi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sketches/pi/</guid>
      <description>She has presences In the Electric view A blinding stew … of plight and magic … A diplomatic Coefficient Bristled into Her Majestic (and few) (This is my first digital drawing, done on Leonardo. The character is based on Loish&amp;rsquo;s Huntress, which is easily my favorite work of hers. I liked it so much that I felt the need to mimic it and finally give this whole digital art thing a try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rough</title>
      <link>/words/2019/rough/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2019/rough/</guid>
      <description>High on Human So very High on Human Yeah, I&amp;#39;m High on Human So many stories and victories The agony And yeah, the drama You know it feeds the Momma This Human High So high! Why fight it (Just live it) Death is withdrawal Birth the next hit No questions now This Human got me crazy lit! High! So high, man Oh, the Human High High on Human Set sails So fairy tale Don&amp;#39;t dwell Ride the Human High &amp;amp; Its blazed-out swell Oh man High as a kite again Thank you, Human Where you been?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heart</title>
      <link>/words/2019/heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2019/heart/</guid>
      <description>It seems so long ago Yet yesterday All the way from the dusk and dawn and dusk again The moon and alleyways Walking past That police car, and trying my best to look n	o	r	m	a	l And then you entered As a Shamaness A fortuneteller And spoke to me In Truth and Majesty In plain words And riddles, too Yes, we spoke in two planes That night In the real and In the surreal (visceral) The problems in the village Were the problems in me .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spike</title>
      <link>/words/2018/spike/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2018/spike/</guid>
      <description>Oh, the prowl The staking howl Sounds on the take A whisper make Where&amp;#39;s your pride Lost one? Looking for a Troubled ton Searching for your size and lies Only to find Your Lion Eyes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leaf</title>
      <link>/notes/2018/leaf/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/notes/2018/leaf/</guid>
      <description>Phenomena is mind control.
In remembrance of July 3rd, 1971.

May you rest in the peace
that you so rightfully deserve,
good sir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wane</title>
      <link>/words/2018/wane/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2018/wane/</guid>
      <description>Ignited praises
Holy mazes
Starbound gazes
Trinity phases
Destiny graces
Multifold faces
Spun laces
Tied cases
Flickering spaces
Spiritual aces
Dancing stasis
Married places
Angelic traces
Deserted sages
World stages
Folly ages
Spellbound cages
Mystic mages
Digging wages
Justice rages</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Side</title>
      <link>/stories/2018/side/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2018/side/</guid>
      <description>With the monitors flickering upon his nearby, dark environment, Ron then wondered further that if the very reality that he is currently experiencing now is indeed a simulation of some sort &amp;ndash; with technology accelerating at a seemingly accelerating rate &amp;ndash; would it eventually culminate in the ability to accurately reflect the reality that Ron was in now?
The idea struck Ron. Is the reality that Ron finds himself in now a result of jumping into a technology or program that started in the same way as he is currently experiencing?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grind</title>
      <link>/stories/2018/grind/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2018/grind/</guid>
      <description>(Based on an actual event.)
“DID ANYONE CALL 911?!” I screamed as I jumped out of my car.
“YES,” a voice rang out plainly to me. I felt stupid for asking. It would end up being my only contribution towards the entire disaster.
The man in his car behind me – Kenneth, I would like to say – had just gotten out of his own vehicle and ran resolutely to the aid of whoever was trapped in the flipped over cold, blue car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pair</title>
      <link>/prayers/2018/pair/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/prayers/2018/pair/</guid>
      <description>To Apollo, the god of strength and truth, from whom I learned the power of taking quiet solitude and the well-rounded value of keeping a well-formed opinion to one’s self. From a great many precepts, you taught me how to find and discern the many sides of an issue, while reserving judgement for only when it is absolutely required. To you, I am indebted to learning patience and fortitude, to understanding the harmonious workings of nature and man, and to keeping such courtesies within the realm of my consciousness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notes</title>
      <link>/documents/notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documents/notes/</guid>
      <description>A little idea I had back in the day. Does the Earth speak to us in notes?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>