<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Words on ossem: a creative space</title>
    <link>/words/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Words on ossem: a creative space</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/words/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rough</title>
      <link>/words/2019/rough/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2019/rough/</guid>
      <description>High on Human So very High on Human Yeah, I&amp;#39;m High on Human So many stories and victories The agony And yeah, the drama You know it feeds the Momma This Human High So high! Why fight it (Just live it) Death is withdrawal Birth the next hit No questions now This Human got me crazy lit! High! So high, man Oh, the Human High High on Human Set sails So fairy tale Don&amp;#39;t dwell Ride the Human High &amp;amp; Its blazed-out swell Oh man High as a kite again Thank you, Human Where you been?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heart</title>
      <link>/words/2019/heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2019/heart/</guid>
      <description>It seems so long ago Yet yesterday All the way from the dusk and dawn and dusk again The moon and alleyways Walking past That police car, and trying my best to look n	o	r	m	a	l And then you entered As a Shamaness A fortuneteller And spoke to me In Truth and Majesty In plain words And riddles, too Yes, we spoke in two planes That night In the real and In the surreal (visceral) The problems in the village Were the problems in me .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spike</title>
      <link>/words/2018/spike/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2018/spike/</guid>
      <description>Oh, the prowl The staking howl Sounds on the take A whisper make Where&amp;#39;s your pride Lost one? Looking for a Troubled ton Searching for your size and lies Only to find Your Lion Eyes </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wane</title>
      <link>/words/2018/wane/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2018/wane/</guid>
      <description>Ignited praises
Holy mazes
Starbound gazes
Trinity phases
Destiny graces
Multifold faces
Spun laces
Tied cases
Flickering spaces
Spiritual aces
Dancing stasis
Married places
Angelic traces
Deserted sages
World stages
Folly ages
Spellbound cages
Mystic mages
Digging wages
Justice rages</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>/words/2018/06/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2018/06/dream/</guid>
      <description>Kneel to feel Steeled will Encompassing expression Congealed predilection Summoned equilibrium Metallic symposium Knights and valor Cherished Savoir Courtly sunrise Inspiring enterprise Sightly scenes God beams Flickering destiny Dreaming symphony Driven signals Lighted particles Summer peak Calling streak Momentum’s chariot Fasten up Diffused negation Saved nations Praising angels Manna prevails </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stone</title>
      <link>/words/2018/06/stone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2018/06/stone/</guid>
      <description>If I cajole, coerce, condescend, disparage, intimidate Another human spirit in attempt to somehow gain the minds, approval, or liking of others Then I have already lost If respect is not shown in a way that reflects and acknowledges My own self in another person’s bone and skin, Having lived such a life as mine with a completely different set of results and perspective Then I have already lost If I try to dominate the indomitable The fellow wild human spirit that runs as free as Nature Itself with me Then I have already lost If I don’t welcome your contrarian view Which illuminates the side of my prey – our prey that which was yet unseen, unknown, and different to me Then I have already lost If I meet your perceived disrespect With my own in actual intent To prove that I am somehow more “right” or “found” than you Then I have already lost </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Light</title>
      <link>/words/2018/light/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2018/light/</guid>
      <description>Strung along gilded hopes And dreams and visions of past There is some angel in these eyes (and the Bright) Reigned for days by spells and lies Oh, these broken, jeweled moons No no, it’s far too soon (the move) Yes, I have shed the Dark and the Shadow. And on the Straits, I crucified Her on the gallows Somewhere beyond Golgotha and Gomorrah She hung high and seaside With four others, screaming wide “HOW COULD YOU DO THIS TO ME?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pale</title>
      <link>/words/2018/pale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2018/pale/</guid>
      <description>She has a predilection For tawdry destinations. She’s had too much (what’s one more?) Just one more. She’s taken the hit. The strife. Oh, the drama. She can’t get enough. She can’t get enough. (She’ll never come down now.) Once all the stars die out. Her angels flame out. Will She pick up this rock again? Or leave it for dead? Star struck. Never lucked out. Just Her cavern of doubt And sworn hallows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One</title>
      <link>/words/2017/one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2017/one/</guid>
      <description>I’ve got a dark eye, yeah. Dipped in marrow. Coated in chaos. Thumbing the lies. Offensive as life. Bathed in bliss. Harnessed in heart. She’s got dark eyes, yeah. Steeped in hallow. Stringing the skies. Suggestive as life. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Since</title>
      <link>/words/2016/since/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2016/since/</guid>
      <description>Something happened in the valley. The strange, and derelict. There are the words to say, to convey. A passing mind’s eye, a mighty shift. Tapestries are folded, in the flock of fools, Sewn together by raging stools. An adventure cut short, only to be abounded, And hounded, by pride and envy. A nature’s wrath comes full force, Only to beg for mercy. A time’s unwind, through space and twine, These are the mystery’s take, through due wine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stake</title>
      <link>/words/2015/stake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2015/stake/</guid>
      <description>Will you not let me be?
(Causal factions)
And if we are not here.
(not in the clear).
It’s not often we are here.
And when I lose the spot we were in,
I become unglued.
The Saints are not happy
With how I play the game.
But to me, it’s all the same.
Battlefields are won with
Patience and poise.
Not reckless noise.
We make a life out of mystery</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pound</title>
      <link>/words/2015/pound/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2015/pound/</guid>
      <description>We are dark. We are deep. We are discrete. She leads me into the mystery. The misery. The ease. Sum of the parts. And the ton. Hash of the gold. Blue hush. Blinded by the metaled bye. Her harsh belt slighted a soft cheek. A family. Tumultuous. Second hindquadrant. Precious immigration. Disguise my blinded eye. She is here. In my clear. How do I hold you? The fear is real. Every night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saved</title>
      <link>/words/2015/saved/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2015/saved/</guid>
      <description>Where hare you?
Are you in the blue.
Are you here in the stead.
Are you here in my head.
I feel the taste.
Electric paste.
The moment between moments.
A calm buzz.
A careening presumption.
A black white hum.
Subtle space.
Can you feel me?
It’s a special space.
A 12 step process.
Five planting.
7 climbing.
Somewhere it is there.
I wear it briefly.
A sudden god.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plot</title>
      <link>/words/2015/plot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2015/plot/</guid>
      <description>She speaks in soft whispers
And I take the messages from
It
And place the binding in you.
Here
She rests in Peace
And confounding bliss
Spires of beauty
Entwined in me.
She’s a part of you, too.
An awkward tirade of sorts
She conspires agenda.
To what was.
What once will be.
Her pleasure is yours.
Will you not act
Upon your time.
I will not.
Singular or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tote</title>
      <link>/words/2014/tote/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2014/tote/</guid>
      <description>So far away
The sun beams
Steal us away
In concrete gutters
We skip and play
So wasted
You sell houses
And I am a wealthy
Prospective buyer
We stroll down heavy
Streets and look over
Cobble-stone driveways
Maybe we&amp;rsquo;ll find a match
And will live happily ever
After and after
Oh look a church
How saintly and
Majestic
Shelled in stained glass
We walk around but
Do not enter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two</title>
      <link>/words/2014/two/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2014/two/</guid>
      <description>Encased in Her desire
I am dressed in Mire.
Second-face
Throughport
Who has second center?
Would you like to sleep?
Essence, pre-absorbed.
She’s in my hind-center.
Images are cheap
A dozen, so to speak.
A mouthpiece is necessary
Will you marry me?
The secret is out
Without a doubt.
And a stop goes to
A cottonmouth.
No play
To this day
We are in the south
Don’t bounce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slang</title>
      <link>/words/2014/slang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2014/slang/</guid>
      <description>Do you hear the sway
Of guns and heart
Of wishes and mantles
Of death and start.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slight</title>
      <link>/words/2014/slight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2014/slight/</guid>
      <description>when the lovers dance
And are swept by
Guiding glances of
Sad sunlight
The gods simple mocking
Of afternoon pleasures
Holidays that are never
Realized.
They
Came to stay. Led astray.
They
Lie awake. Stranded takes.
Misty ghosts dance upon
Misty houses broken down
They laugh and flee.
There is no glee.
A coward&amp;rsquo;s paradise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marks</title>
      <link>/words/2014/marks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2014/marks/</guid>
      <description>This is my notebook.
There are many like this one.
But this one is mine.
With this notebook.
I can alight realms.
And destroy a people.
I am a fleshy weight
Bundled in tome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Please</title>
      <link>/words/2014/please/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2014/please/</guid>
      <description>She breathes in my opposite Counterbearing to my darewit, She billows in gallows far from me. And I, in esteem, carry streets of dreams Collective arms and nations. Breathe. I am the ends of me. D96 Premonitions are not unlost. We peer into the sanctuary. We are in the posthaste mortuary. Songs are written, foes are beaten. Adversaries tell the tale, warriors ring the bell. Short-timers sell, Cretans foretell. An ocean for a lover, Conscious compromise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Break</title>
      <link>/words/2014/break/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2014/break/</guid>
      <description>She stirs in the wind. She sits at my foot and we drift. In consecrated skies, we kiss. She is no home to me. She is so mean to me. Judged, on a half-steak makes me break. I ascend into Her calm. She takes me as I am. She is no savior. And when I commune with Her, Universes dissipate with Bright. She teaches how to hold my sword. And I learn how to make my word.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ton</title>
      <link>/words/2014/ton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2014/ton/</guid>
      <description>Into me. Breathe. q. Breathe deep. I construct theis guy. Neurotic hackery? A piece of me. Is there anything wrong? Is there anything right? Of f to the ocorner of ahthatht guy. Let’s’ hit that; Let’s do. I might migraine to the 2nd soul. I might be in your room. In our room. I omight. Sencidn., Interview. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bow</title>
      <link>/words/2014/bow/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2014/bow/</guid>
      <description>When She kisses my moonlight, I hide in burrowed screams. And I, in my own light. Know Her sunbeams. My worthless plight of day. Her might of play. Taunting. The Earth bends below Her. It sings joyed terror. And I, in my dance. Lurch in acquiesce. Stupidity rinses my strength away. Down such a gloried fade. Days of promise seem so far away. No angels stand near. Knocks of wine. Colors spin so fine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T</title>
      <link>/words/2014/t/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2014/t/</guid>
      <description>To give carely. To receive bountifully. We are the psychology of you. And us. The aisles of contempt. And anguish. Your Love is here. Be clear. The trips of dreams In me. The obsession of wealth. The obsession of Time. The trips within me Are beam. A smoky horizon, Breeding impermanence. A dangerous occupation. In the flesh, You’re letting your work run in. The work runs in within I’ll trail after that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trust</title>
      <link>/words/2013/trust/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/trust/</guid>
      <description>When She cries in me. (I am insane). And the words we make. (are just a game). How does one go mad? (sure you’re not glad?) Is it a suit and bow tie? (don’t forget to die). How do I channel you? (you’re still living). How do I level you? (you’re still breathing). These words we use. (are just a game). Mystery tells. (another story). A space to His own. (it’s His kingdom, after all).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tramp</title>
      <link>/words/2013/tramp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/tramp/</guid>
      <description>A god, Broken into billions of pieces. A piece is you. To gather the pieces is… a clue. Are you a piece of me? Am I a piece of you? How do I see this piece of me? Where? Shattered. Assembled whole. Ocean images. You must show something for your efforts. Something. There are trysts in these parts. There are trusts, too. I have the karma divide. She is not very nice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pure</title>
      <link>/words/2013/pure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/pure/</guid>
      <description>Thoughts and dreams… and mystery. She sings to me With Such Broken Promises. I cling to Her twisted stains. For my life. (in disbelief) In terror, I am Her puppet. In life, I am Her master. In troubled keep. I dance Her wake. I wrap myself in Her mistakes. For Her misery is my desire. A steadfast plan of mire. And desolate beauty. Seen. Lost in Her seams. I long for Her lonely glance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tempt</title>
      <link>/words/2013/tempt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/tempt/</guid>
      <description>I is the drink. Do I get paid to think? Cummervescence. Pleasance. Trysto. Manifesto. Where is the mindset? Where is the bodytet? No Pain. No Fear. Play your hand. It’s in the sand. What’s air to you? Just asking. Air is nice. It’s not ice. My crazy little friend. Chipzah. To me, it means prosperity. See, I dance around. Unexpopound(ed). And when the moon’s not right. We solicify it. Same ol’ me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Try</title>
      <link>/words/2013/try/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/try/</guid>
      <description>She lights my world. In me. And i. am. Hers. I echo through Her landscape. Her sounds bound in bliss. Lighted by fire. Seething The Bright. I slide down Her magnificent high. And then She becomes me. The absurdity. I reign Her chaos so suddenly. We grasp upon the signs of dance. I am drowned in Her expanse. We celebrate the Godspace. Broken like bread on a tree’s face. She whispers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thing</title>
      <link>/words/2013/thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/thing/</guid>
      <description>A lover’s space, A hint of the unthinkable. A chord of trust. A messenger in God’s space. A forsaken plan. A song of pain. A coward’s trace, A trace of the predictable, A patio’s preface. A repetitive apology. A muse speaks. A maze breaks. A dance turns to words. A word turns to God. A riddle becomes God. A solution begins, A friendship trends, A team mends. A cycle of truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tea</title>
      <link>/words/2013/tea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/tea/</guid>
      <description>In my state. Counting. 0000000000000. T-state? Is this an edge push or not? An edgue –push state? (Demonstration?) A pish. A puwsh. A blinding. Push spiy. Spoy.. Qqqqqq believing., And onccccccce a;; beliving is done. A student of crime. Now, that’s the first thing that’s mmade sense…. Thru. These broken deade keyboards, The then sealed. Your eyes. Open.d. Miracle. Whart. Is the message. Pretenser. Pretenser? What is the mesaage? Q	whqat is your messsaagwe?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stand</title>
      <link>/words/2013/stand/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/stand/</guid>
      <description>She’s got a dirty eye Placed in me She’s got a filthy spirit Dancing A dirty eye Not far from peace A filthy spirit Pleasing A time comes Wrapped in strands Of stars And rapture Her voice Here Her space Vision Entering upon the Sun Joining my broken body Pieces and dust Mixed destiny Stirred vastness I am Her wasted soldier Sword in broken hand I tremble Fortified She seals me Forged in night She takes me Shadows breaking sand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Short</title>
      <link>/words/2013/short/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/short/</guid>
      <description>Are you crying? Are you dead? Order. Prestigue. sAfter all that… Yoiur at a hakter, Is nthere an aex”? Your study yoouuuur ahit/. Youuuuve been preshifted. Is that goofd? You habve n o understanding. Ill dance to me. T m humanity.\ \\	\	\\\	\\ Well. It’s us;. You’re such a chhhhhhhhhhhhheater. Flesh. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dirt</title>
      <link>/words/2013/dirt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2013/dirt/</guid>
      <description>Strike a dime’s eye. It’s your might. Are we children? Or are we dancers? A child dances upon leaves. Who are we? Figure it out. A cold doubt. We are the Kings and Queens of Mystery Eternal. A golden sun upon yourself. Am I you? Am I him? (frame). Deny the God upon your servant’s brow. In your head are we? Then what are we here for? I fold my eyelid over itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Link</title>
      <link>/words/2012/link/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/link/</guid>
      <description>And here. We are beautifully broken. So perfectly lost. How did we get here? So fairytale. A lost ship has sunk. From its coast, it dares not tell. Angels swoop upon the treasure. (it is their pleasure) Collect the gold. It’s greed, after all. Timeless classic. Pace a time’s forth. (are you in love again?) There is something to be bought. A price that is sought. There are stories to be won.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bring</title>
      <link>/words/2012/bring/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/bring/</guid>
      <description>And fell, the hammer did fell. The pressure, misfit. Hey, did you just make that? It’s my art, so yes. Side room. Is this side room ours? ? Wow. You stretched it. (hard). Why won’t you hit your heart? A dance of pleasure. Aced of bacon. A slide show. Prescence. Hey,. That’s wrong. Cornerstone is set. Hm, Milk and gasoline. (set us free). Where’s the pleasure principle? TELL ME! The guided crosses will know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ask</title>
      <link>/words/2012/ask/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/ask/</guid>
      <description>It’s a dead end rodeo. Which way will you go. I choose peace. I choose mayhem. That’s funny. That’s not where you were Seconds ago. Tell you what. (we’ll flip a coin). Flip One. (here it goes). Flip two (here’s his campaign manager). Flip three. (here’s to you and me). Get that out of your system? Grind and mind, actually. I’m sure. OK? A protective bith slap… Is he,… watching his language?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Line</title>
      <link>/words/2012/line/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/line/</guid>
      <description>Well, I&amp;rsquo;ve got
The world in my eyes and
The Universe in my Heart
I&amp;rsquo;m not sure where to start
Maybe with you.
We&amp;rsquo;ll ride the blue
Break the clear
Ride the clear
Run the fear
Be the fear
In your presence
The choice is clear
I&amp;rsquo;m your terrorist
I&amp;rsquo;m your hero
I&amp;rsquo;m the everything
You don&amp;rsquo;t know
I&amp;rsquo;m the terrorist
I&amp;rsquo;m the hero
There&amp;rsquo;s no telling
The seed I sow</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set</title>
      <link>/words/2012/set/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/set/</guid>
      <description>The Sun sets, yet,
The World in Her Eyes
The Wings of Her Flight
The Sun sets, yet.
The Sun sets, yet,
The dare to change
The Air of Change
The Sun sets, yet.
The Sun sets, yet,
The nation of sorrow
The heart of tomorrow
The Sun sets, yet.
The Sun sets, yet,
The happiness within Her
The peace beneath Her.
The Sun sets, yet.
The Sun sets, yet,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Be</title>
      <link>/words/2012/be/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/be/</guid>
      <description>How do you dissolve nerousis? With a toothpick. Now, dance with me. I ain’t hitting that with a glass case. Now a vase. Heyyy! Get it! (alignment) Just being honest. Now, back to that honesty. Does it cost you? There’s a price, isn’t there? Watch the table. TH e table is ours. What do you see? A beautiful song. So not right. What do you hear? An anthem. Now we’re rockin’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tame</title>
      <link>/words/2012/tame/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/tame/</guid>
      <description>In my dreams
I am tucked in Her sleep.
Awakened. Silenced.
In Her fears
She is brought to silenced knee.
A knee to here?
So far from me.
Wet. The streets are soaked.
And the drain is dazed.
Honeyphazed.
A prerecording.
A sonboarding.
A boundary.
A dance space.
In this place, a secret message.
In this family, a tone is set.
Dry rock.
You mean an ice cold precipice
Rock solid can challenge the rights up here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cave</title>
      <link>/words/2012/cave/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/cave/</guid>
      <description>Your brain is hot. Ot’s thinking. A pressure monet. A pressure taking. Is this your wallet. Is this your monhey. Hahaha… I disagree. Who is that guy anyways? Well, I’ll tell you a story. Blah blah, Should you disrupt that one. Thos one. Well politics. Politics are fun. Now, where did the humor go? My humor? Your humour? The humor is here. You watched him as a necessary element. Let me place this base.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trim</title>
      <link>/words/2012/trim/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/trim/</guid>
      <description>Heated dance. Billowing hair. Her look. In my locked cell. She gives me grace. Spaced shoulders. Pumping… This is her crowd. By the hand, She takes me. I feel her sweat. Her heat takes me. Jumping, Her look. unfolds my world. And the way she is Makes me wonder what will be. Supple responsibility. In here. We are partners. Assembled whole. A problem is just a label. We see the stage for what it is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chain</title>
      <link>/words/2012/chain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/chain/</guid>
      <description>Chained.
Behind blacked walls.
A screen appears.
She appears to me.
Human form.
Speaking. On authority.
And now, the quest begins.
An innerspace of wills.
To read the ether.
To provide the circumstance.
The mist dissolves in sunlight.
Tremendous bright.
Her energy radiates beauty.
Dissipating lock and key.
And here. In our time.
We play the tones of life.’
And wonder the keys and charms within.
Can I make this better?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sense</title>
      <link>/words/2012/sense/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/sense/</guid>
      <description>Well, she’s a righteous shortcoming I want to be her. To dance her. To lick her skin deep within She knows my heartache (It’s a sick mistake.) I can’t break her trust I must trip in her eyes It’s no surprise Her heart tries to capture That what is in me When I soak in the ripples of her bliss I cannot dismiss that I No longer No longer No longer Know me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perch</title>
      <link>/words/2012/perch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/perch/</guid>
      <description>She breaks upon Her
Perch, timeless.
We are the golden gods
Of a silenced age.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rhyme</title>
      <link>/words/2012/rhyme/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/rhyme/</guid>
      <description>I gauged her thighs carefully. Broken skirt. Her paw had summit. I fathomed a conversation. But instead I settled into Her. Gauging again. I watch her thighs. She sees my moves. I reangle. WAY overcompensate. She flees. At the sight of me. Hands clawing. Turn right. Into left. Mirror passes pillar. She peeks past plastic star. Am I too far? Too distant? I drive. Not too fast. Not too slow. But there’s a jacket on the car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beach</title>
      <link>/words/2012/beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/beach/</guid>
      <description>Chipper chapper. Let’s stop this right here. Isn’t this the same as the last? Twelve hours at a time is a long time To read minds. Isn’t it nice to be around people again? To what end? What’s your purpose. To me, Everyone Is poetry. Dancing energy. Your spirit is captured in me. You’re keeping note of names, I like that. Letters, spelling. A nice chat. On a sunny afternoon. The 10:10 would appreciate that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Same</title>
      <link>/words/2012/same/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/same/</guid>
      <description>That was my card. That was our card. She flipped it on its face. I knew it before we grabbed it. The hobbit post-faced it. Row of ladies on the left. Row of guys on the right. Fat bastard’s in my chair The queen’s gotta pair. It’s time to go. It’s time to row. 9:07PM specifically. The trees are leaves. Our eyes met. Consistently. An eye-five. Pleased me. She asked my name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fine</title>
      <link>/words/2012/fine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/fine/</guid>
      <description>When she smiles They, smile. It makes me wonder why I feel this way. And all the connections, and emotions. To deal with them. In your way. And my way. There are very bad things in this world. Very good things, too. Which ones do you choose? We continue to choose both. Imbalance would be treason. If “they” know everything about you, What is there to fear? To be ashamed? To be guilty of?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live</title>
      <link>/words/2012/live/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/live/</guid>
      <description>Stand
Marching band
Witches bring us</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gut</title>
      <link>/words/2012/gut/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/gut/</guid>
      <description>Answer the question, Claire. There’s an act in all of us. So then, you’re not a … What was the question again? That’s funny, I forgot the question as well. So what are we doing here? Seeking truth. I’m seeking destruction. Hot. Cold. Up. Down. Left Right White Black Peace Trouble Treble Bass Spirit Soul Light Sound Science Art Life Religion Normalcy Anxiety Honesty Trixstery Light Shadow Flattery Stealing Child Adult Adult Child Correcting Cheating Principle Law Good Great Slow Fast Self Phenomena </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modes</title>
      <link>/words/2012/modes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/modes/</guid>
      <description>Sleepy eye
Angry shaman
Wry guy
Creating</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love</title>
      <link>/words/2012/love/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/love/</guid>
      <description>Death. Life. Is that your wife?
Soldiers understand the meanings.
Just don&amp;rsquo;t think of these while sleeping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I</title>
      <link>/words/2012/i/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/i/</guid>
      <description>I’ll step into your garden While following my bliss. Bliss, while misunderstood, is just a property of your path. It’s a compensation of thinking. That is: feeling. Back to your garden: There is a circle. There are two trees. Twins, I’d say. And then there’s this creepy shed. The leaves paint a path outside of the circle. All the while, I keep my eye steady for the people that might approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tip</title>
      <link>/words/2012/tip/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/tip/</guid>
      <description>Levitating drink off the side bar.
I thought you were smart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mine</title>
      <link>/words/2012/mine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/mine/</guid>
      <description>It is not good for man to be alone
So when man begins to dance again
The steps placed square within him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prime</title>
      <link>/words/2012/prime/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/prime/</guid>
      <description>enter right
Through the left.
Your frame still
Manifests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let</title>
      <link>/words/2012/let/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/let/</guid>
      <description>How do I live up to this? Looking to the side stage. My Stage. You caught it, you bought it. I’m flipping caps here. I don’t think I can dance this stepfloor. … and then… “I’m sort of interested in honesty.” Ya, what is honesty, anyways? Honesty is reaching for the wrong bottle. And knowing it. Honesty is predicting the future. Then facing it. Honesty is consistency. Didn’t you say that consistency is key?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lick</title>
      <link>/words/2012/lick/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/lick/</guid>
      <description>Fire up your gods.
R
A valued goddess
Has stories in her chest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sell</title>
      <link>/words/2012/sell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/sell/</guid>
      <description>What are your signs? Would I invite Her to church? There’s a roundwheel going around here. Flow the spigot. The spigot is good. Spigggots are also nice, as well. ARE WE IN HELL??? A flower will suit you well. But next time, the flower is there. Not here. All of these multitudes of possibilities. Your area is weak. Where are these starstruck adventures as youth? UNCOMPROMISING, SIR???\ Well, philosophy is one thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gift</title>
      <link>/words/2012/gift/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2012/gift/</guid>
      <description>The cars sound empty And hollow. The band swings mighty hallowed. We walk with saints. She’s the lead singer. Man she can belt a tune. And there’s the story teller. Telling your fortunes. A roving band. Walking the streets of netherland. Strange talent of gods. Speak with us. Calling / sparking / presence. Man, let’s load up on the spirits. Poets of concrete. No longer discrete. Where did you get that shirt?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pay</title>
      <link>/words/2011/pay/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/pay/</guid>
      <description>alright.
If what you&amp;rsquo;re going through
Man if this is your story.
Bring it forth right.
Symmetry is not our friend tonight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trench</title>
      <link>/words/2011/trench/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/trench/</guid>
      <description>What???
How did I get here????
Ruffled feather.
This is all nonsense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bright</title>
      <link>/words/2011/12/bright/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/12/bright/</guid>
      <description>orange bread
Strange dreads
She speaks to me</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your</title>
      <link>/words/2011/your/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/your/</guid>
      <description>stand proud
Impermanence
Is ray-bound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time</title>
      <link>/words/2011/time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/time/</guid>
      <description>Here I am The king of my own very canal. A thought Impulse. A derision. Cloudy thoughts. Enter the mindtrain. The purity of extra thought. Loud and clear. An extra ear. Of yours. No way are you here. No way. Strike my hand. Will it bleed. Surface cut. If there is a problem here, I … Chasm of pronouncement. There’s this angle. And this image. And then… A great thought over here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Land</title>
      <link>/words/2011/land/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/land/</guid>
      <description>Will be times. Many times in my life. Where I will simply tone out. Zone out. It’s as if I’m the bell. And the window. It’s as if this is it.	This is all I have. And then I’m called back. A blink. A mystery. A challenge. And then it all seems so foolish. Second guessing. Neighborhooding. Bringing back the last days. Some days. These days. It’s not here. You wish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sand</title>
      <link>/words/2011/sand/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/sand/</guid>
      <description>A cool effervescence Of some sort. Don’t do what you do. Do what you do. To me, There are two forces in life, There’s the reptile And there’s the Space Angel === The art of these two warring fractions Is you. What does it mean To be free? A free man. Last time I checked. There are lots of definitions of free. We’re not gonna get there, are we? Someone over here says… Sin virtue and vice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Splash</title>
      <link>/words/2011/splash/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/splash/</guid>
      <description>Shamanic blessings
Surprises
The king&amp;rsquo;s court arises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grid</title>
      <link>/words/2011/grid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/grid/</guid>
      <description>in her wet den of twisted charm
My soul breathes awake
Hallow echo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plain</title>
      <link>/words/2011/plain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/plain/</guid>
      <description>I saw it. No. You had it wrong. You can slay something. And you can love something. It’s not the same, Gentlemen. Can we go back to ground zero. What is this hero’s business anyways? Consciousness? Ego? OK. Once there was this Dragon. It lived in its nest. A far-reaching cliff of sorts. Now this Dragon was very natural In how it behaved. It flew the skies of paradise. High brow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lake</title>
      <link>/words/2011/lake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/lake/</guid>
      <description>Scorpish scales Descend Appropriately. We contend. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Line</title>
      <link>/words/2011/line/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/line/</guid>
      <description>Sting serpentine ritual High accord She sung to me Her song. I uh just form here. And then. Magic happen. In this space. Where we were once. Proud and Independent. Without the aid of others. Spiral happenstance. A dance. Mm. Wings unfurl. On the outset.-ide. Oh, you want me to finish this sentence? Well, I have been known to plow forth. To break the seal Of a sacrifice. It’s a big deal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toy</title>
      <link>/words/2011/toy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/toy/</guid>
      <description>I watched those crows.
I watched that fog.
Those signs&amp;hellip;
Pointed one way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zen</title>
      <link>/words/2011/zen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/zen/</guid>
      <description>Solid sword
We are katana.
When that bangs on a tree&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brace</title>
      <link>/words/2011/brace/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/brace/</guid>
      <description>The Warrior sits upright With his sword belted Tightly. He brings his chest to bare. Something of a precious artifact. The swinging Indian scout drops over his stout log A bit of a fog. Over the horizon there’s a Message from the cul-de-sac. The Warrior. Grasps his handle. Darkened wisp of candle. He clings. Nightly. &amp;#34;Shouldn’t your majesty be. Twisting a different message?&amp;#34; The swinging Indian scout. Laughs wildly. The others are just.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall</title>
      <link>/words/2011/fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/fall/</guid>
      <description>On your laughter.
It is bliss.
But do cover that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nine</title>
      <link>/words/2011/nine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/nine/</guid>
      <description>Speak in code.
I&amp;rsquo;m your bro.
Circle your braids.
They are beautiful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crack</title>
      <link>/words/2011/crack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/crack/</guid>
      <description>Check one check two. They comin’ for you. Check it thrice. Gawd damn. Sir, that’s not very nice. Cup the hands. Now. Straight up. Saw that action. Fire fire. No pants here. If there were, Well, The dashes and mashes. Goodness gracious. Can you imagine? We can. Our crew can. And we do. What’s it to you? Back and forth. See-saw. It’s a bit of a mystery Like fire. Once it catches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curl</title>
      <link>/words/2011/curl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/curl/</guid>
      <description>Seriously.
Why is sex so weird.
No way will it meet strange.
Ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glum</title>
      <link>/words/2011/glum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/glum/</guid>
      <description>Your infection is a
Badge.
I will draw it</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last</title>
      <link>/words/2011/last/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/last/</guid>
      <description>If it&amp;rsquo;s offered
Fill the coffers.
Her smile lost me.
The twins have a
lovely mistress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love</title>
      <link>/words/2011/love/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/love/</guid>
      <description>A strange house
Phenomena is your key
Watch your mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mean</title>
      <link>/words/2011/mean/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/mean/</guid>
      <description>A time
Awkward placement.
emotional disrupt.
Disruptured rapture.
Blinded lines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Purse</title>
      <link>/words/2011/purse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/purse/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s this about?
Really.
All I know.
You broke a 20.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test</title>
      <link>/words/2011/10/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/10/test/</guid>
      <description>Reject me.
Be with me.
Your son. Has.
Curious behavior.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rain</title>
      <link>/words/2011/rain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/rain/</guid>
      <description>Wings pressed on
Sweat and dew.
She is in love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stew</title>
      <link>/words/2011/stew/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/stew/</guid>
      <description>Stumbling lords
Of pawned mascots
Psychic clans clamor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Say</title>
      <link>/words/2011/say/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/say/</guid>
      <description>Let’s walk over this tripwire. It’s a finewire. Superfire. Dancestep. Aged regret. Don’t talk yet. Moon dance. Hunted stance. Wolves in the background. And by our side. Simple outlets. Forced blocks. Don’t knock. Home base. Troubled base. A friend of who’s friend? On this battleground. It might be sound. But. I don’t get it. Ya, me too. Why would I keep you closer. If you’re my brother. And all that jazz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dot</title>
      <link>/words/2011/dot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/dot/</guid>
      <description>Hands off the mothership.
Are you ready to commit
This ritual or what?
In.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hub</title>
      <link>/words/2011/hub/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/hub/</guid>
      <description>Fuck children.
Let&amp;rsquo;s get twisted
And run through Ikea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lo</title>
      <link>/words/2011/lo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/lo/</guid>
      <description>Something happened. Before it pretenseed. Super yawning. That’s right… magic. Let’s not change the super charged. SUPER CALIFLOWERPRELIOUS Since you asked. Jesuits wished they had the same. Precedence as this. It’s a matter. Of listening To the sky wishing it were shy. And then a mishmash. Supper. Eggs and cheese. Q wish you were me. From so far away? We’re done here. Yay then. Meet and then Meat too. Sausage and chicken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tell</title>
      <link>/words/2011/tell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/tell/</guid>
      <description>Well that&amp;rsquo;s a game.
And this one too.
I have a friend.
But uh, you ,
Certainly ask a lot of quest9</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clear</title>
      <link>/words/2011/clear/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/clear/</guid>
      <description>Soul soaked in disarray
Blinding sunstream
Staked through
Broken vision</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ton</title>
      <link>/words/2011/ton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/ton/</guid>
      <description>Yo dawg I was watching this fly right In my room And it just straight up gave me an Ego Butt To let me know who’s dawg, yo. Alright ok… let’s step away from that one for just a second. I sort of set things up in just.\ Up. Quadrants. If you please. Um. Um Um. Yum Yum Yum. Tum tum tum. Yes? Huh? Huh? Ok. Let’s get right into this shading business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tense</title>
      <link>/words/2011/tense/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/tense/</guid>
      <description>It is a troubled sport
How will you recollect
Your deepest memory?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trap</title>
      <link>/words/2011/trap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/trap/</guid>
      <description>Who is your favorite
Teammate?
a friend descends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Troup</title>
      <link>/words/2011/troup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/troup/</guid>
      <description>Dream of your hero. And then you know. The secret songs. Hallowed flow. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cope</title>
      <link>/words/2011/cope/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/cope/</guid>
      <description>Something mightily going on with this Virgo business. and then the rest of us. We might pee on another man’s teepee? Let’s just get that one out of the way. There’s a predisposition to attend. You know. Like the kind you used to. Some might consider it… Who are these “some” ? Are they the new “They?” … How did you sleep last night? Quite mightily I must say. Was it assisted?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drive</title>
      <link>/words/2011/drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/drive/</guid>
      <description>Secrets are fun. Secrets in this one. There’s a certain. Rope. A dope. Sucka. Played. And now you. On the sidewalk. Cheek against Steel and concrete. Messy barriers. I’m sure they won’t Be harassing us no more. If you cut a tree in two? What will it do? Will it dance? Prance? .. I know the answer to this one. Look outside your window. Will you? Seriously. Check it out. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cap</title>
      <link>/words/2011/cap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/cap/</guid>
      <description>What if your honesty
Led to nobility
Your presence has
No place for her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dust</title>
      <link>/words/2011/dust/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/dust/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve made it
At what cost.
Indignant.
Cemetery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fly</title>
      <link>/words/2011/fly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/fly/</guid>
      <description>We have placed lungs
Breathed air
No despair.
VP bio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Found</title>
      <link>/words/2011/found/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/found/</guid>
      <description>I would dip into the underground. To be flu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space</title>
      <link>/words/2011/space/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/space/</guid>
      <description>Indian giver.
Marry her.
God I miss her face.
And body.
Grace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star</title>
      <link>/words/2011/star/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/star/</guid>
      <description>What is life?
It&amp;rsquo;s inside of you.
Where&amp;rsquo;s the door?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sum</title>
      <link>/words/2011/sum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/sum/</guid>
      <description>One time.
Two time.
Precious energ7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tough</title>
      <link>/words/2011/tough/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/tough/</guid>
      <description>Secret bloodlines
Steal her laugh time.
She squeals.
Secret peels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tow</title>
      <link>/words/2011/tow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/tow/</guid>
      <description>Dark whores.
Creepy vaginas.
Trepid markstains.
Supple gameday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trip</title>
      <link>/words/2011/trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/trip/</guid>
      <description>Starry entrance
I&amp;rsquo;ve stripped her mind
Memories of that one time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two</title>
      <link>/words/2011/two/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/two/</guid>
      <description>Your message
Makes my brain
Hang out of my sausage.
Second quadrant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Us</title>
      <link>/words/2011/us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/us/</guid>
      <description>Sycophant
Would you place
Your miscreant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arc</title>
      <link>/words/2011/09/arc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/09/arc/</guid>
      <description>Shifting angles
Dancing principles.
A certain birdie knows
Your deepest shows</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bounce</title>
      <link>/words/2011/bounce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/bounce/</guid>
      <description>You might read me.
I&amp;rsquo;ve read a plenty.
There&amp;rsquo;s heartache.
Within. Trees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drum</title>
      <link>/words/2011/drum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/drum/</guid>
      <description>You like
Hard strike
Maybe she
Will let you be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lie</title>
      <link>/words/2011/lie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/lie/</guid>
      <description>Infinity
Trust aplenty
She has brown eyes
Something says tryst .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pound</title>
      <link>/words/2011/pound/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/pound/</guid>
      <description>Something stakes me
Relieves me.
Cupboard basket.
Cake smash it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tall</title>
      <link>/words/2011/tall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/tall/</guid>
      <description>Sister&amp;rsquo;s keeper.
Principle matters.
Namesake.
Place date.
Your sake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Truth</title>
      <link>/words/2011/truth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/truth/</guid>
      <description>Not glory
Woman
Not woman
God</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Want</title>
      <link>/words/2011/want/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/want/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking me
Unlocks your eyes
Disguise those ugly
Questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>War</title>
      <link>/words/2011/war/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/war/</guid>
      <description>Who brought
How taught.
Something simple.
Complex pimple.
Aced face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Price</title>
      <link>/words/2011/price/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/price/</guid>
      <description>To be removed from the tit Of any legacy. It’s not something we take lightly. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test</title>
      <link>/words/2011/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/test/</guid>
      <description>What does it mean to take a knee? Will you watch it with me? There’s a deeper meaning in Everything that we do. A correspondence. A coalescence. When you sit there. And test the boundaries of others. There’s a certain prospect. Of rejection. When this rejection becomes part of you. You stand upon a pedestal of Perspective. When this perspective has sat upon you. You know your place. Now then, Let us continue?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brook</title>
      <link>/words/2011/brook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/brook/</guid>
      <description>Twisted twilight
Spiral cemetery.
Release your mind.
Now you&amp;rsquo;re into me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hair</title>
      <link>/words/2011/hair/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/hair/</guid>
      <description>Dangling bride of eyes
Pressing danger
Staffed leer
She doesn&amp;rsquo;t know
Bangs of fear</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haze</title>
      <link>/words/2011/haze/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/haze/</guid>
      <description>In our damp labyrinth:
Strange creatures
Burrowed Fire
Stirred Soul</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meek</title>
      <link>/words/2011/meek/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/meek/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a candy cane forest
Of death and mist
Coated lullabyes
Singing west</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whip</title>
      <link>/words/2011/whip/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/whip/</guid>
      <description>Where&amp;rsquo;s the sky?
It&amp;rsquo;s your twisted might.
A slight game.
Where&amp;rsquo;s the muse of
Your plastered right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nick</title>
      <link>/words/2011/nick/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/nick/</guid>
      <description>Littleindaaaaaaaaaaaaan chief. Let’s be brief. There’s a certain. Perspective. Some would say they miss you. Under some tissue. And if that tissue is you? Would you presumpuouptuous new? Now now see? These parts. You’ve never seen. These are some children. Mistresses. Something. Become of this? It’s this code. You might see, Once twice? Want to see more? FUCK YOUR SICOMORE TREE!! YOU WANT THIS PRESENCE??? Child please. Present your Bissom belly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pass</title>
      <link>/words/2011/pass/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/pass/</guid>
      <description>I touch the mindstream.
I feel the chaos.
I peel your fervor.
I am your velvet.
Trickle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twice</title>
      <link>/words/2011/twice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/twice/</guid>
      <description>Pouted mouth suckles
Loaded metal
Dagger.
Make it come baby.
Too late.
Gray wake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Once</title>
      <link>/words/2011/once/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/once/</guid>
      <description>She&amp;rsquo;s happiest
When&amp;rsquo;s she&amp;rsquo;s weightless
Drifting into gray Depths.
Heartless laughter.
Tribal disaster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grime</title>
      <link>/words/2011/grime/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/grime/</guid>
      <description>Shaking paw.
High desire.
Her noted palace.
Mire.
Notes and color.
Introduction and mayhem.
It&amp;rsquo;s a feud of mother.
Father.
Let&amp;rsquo;s battle this brother.
To the Technicolor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mow</title>
      <link>/words/2011/mow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/mow/</guid>
      <description>Her soul is desolate.
Her angel is a liquid slate.
Here and now.
A placement of soul
Shifting Netherlands.
She has the key as Her sword.
I watch Her weep brightly, foreword.
And then her.
&amp;ndash; her dagger runs deep in dreamscape
I awake in a bloody escape.
Where does her slithering organ end?
Not a friend. Here everything
is below board.
Soaring before.
And now
Not so clear.
Some fear in those crystal</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shred</title>
      <link>/words/2011/shred/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/shred/</guid>
      <description>She sits with me
Full tilt as the sidewalk
Melts between us
Dirty devils steal one of us
She&amp;rsquo;s a sidearm
And her arm is a
Bandolier
Of crazy years
Some say She dissipates
Crazy 8&amp;rsquo;s
Oh no stay away
She has this mighty fine stack
Of powder
Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t want to be Her
But I know I know I&amp;rsquo;ll be on
On that porch soon
Kicking off my shoes.
She dances blind within</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shake</title>
      <link>/words/2011/shake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/shake/</guid>
      <description>A caged animal. Markings on the floor Indicate A separate subsidy Of consolidation. Friends. A plenty. The evidence suggests Brutal undertakings Of a swift investment Only to be turned over Into a long-term contingent. Separately, there seems to be a motion Of an activity /// where was we? There’s something of a phenomena with this process. Maybe you get this. You have your first thought. And then there’s a second. And then another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speck</title>
      <link>/words/2011/speck/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/speck/</guid>
      <description>She descends In winged dominance Over barren waters My fear is entranced Holy reverberations Mountains quiver. High-winged creatures clap Distanced, they circle Her air. Time caves in my space She cups my broken waste. I am packed meat in Her crusted cocoon. I cry Her wasted tear. Blue sky above and near. Salted demons dance On thirsted tongue. And now, in Her rigid rock-womb A bloody song is rung. Ears bleed forth I’ve lost sight of Her sun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arc</title>
      <link>/words/2011/arc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/arc/</guid>
      <description>Step Four. Nothing more. Nothing less. Universe can be explained to you. To me. Your answer is your key. It’s simple. Masterpiece. A matter of relativity. You hold in your hands this matter. It’s a silver platter. Subject to respect Circumspection Restoration. Your spirit holds The inseminated images Of cinema. Unfolding your mind In a myriad of different fathoms. A bird’s beak is a delicate name, madam. In this Scorpio’s nest, a Brother brings his best.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snow</title>
      <link>/words/2011/snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/snow/</guid>
      <description>Second step. Let’s place me and you In your shoes. What do you choose? Child You are a foster Fire. In this space. Time for this Party To be a tardy prostitute. Dare I solute. To your mighty Promiscuous ways. But, darling please. What does Prometheus weigh? You might kiss to begin. But this breakfast has already committed sin. The stars in your eyes. Much obliged. Hold and Grant your authorship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pour</title>
      <link>/words/2011/pour/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/pour/</guid>
      <description>Cousins of Dionysus Dance your might Around the centered pole Eerie delight The ground swallows your Magicians and sorcerers whole. The troubled elves gasp They laugh inside Back around and around Skip those feet Marching beat. The pole grows wider Your blood runs in cider. Human drama binds/runs the casting spell Dwelling gnomes Double-shaking shoulders Dusted tomes Thick ash smolders Grasping collective Threads of spiraling glee We dance with me. She prances heartache with them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Air</title>
      <link>/words/2011/air/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/air/</guid>
      <description>What is this life I lead. Is it a disease. A second ease. Slowly. Slowly. Patience is a virtue. Yes. Have I made a monster out of this? A rubbing of the chaos. First step. Let us begin. It’s something of an underbelly. A fatboy in disguise. Running after his demise. He wishes his wisdom Buried in broken tides. There are spirits in these Trees. Not just you. Not just me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saint</title>
      <link>/words/2011/saint/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/saint/</guid>
      <description>Do you here pronounce these hands To enjoy The placement of space and time. To embrace the holy remembrance Of the Holy white. To Eat the air. To feel the prenumbrance Of You. Together. United. Let’s watch both of you dance Unto the Holy Lights. Let us place you in A Mighty Delight. Be Blessed and Welcomed To Our Kindred. Bringing you in our heed. A supple steed. Let us all pronounce you Light unto All.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whale</title>
      <link>/words/2011/whale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/whale/</guid>
      <description>A little refresher course for all you numerologists out there. Who’s to blame? All eyes on me. If you please. It’s a delegation.	Predilection. It’s a workshop. Post-mop. Operation. A post-mortem. A mirror on the wall. Watch those who are watching you. And you’ll see. It’s a sea. Of bluegrass. Simple glass. Brotherhood. Misunderstood. Malfunction. Sister break. Let’s watch these words we share. It’s imperative. We declare. Simpleton. Singleton. It might be whiskey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out</title>
      <link>/words/2011/out/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/out/</guid>
      <description>And how you would just stir In that twilight haze That backlight painted my mind With soft expression Of your lost soul My hand would stare up at you Awaiting our first dance And I would lay back and watch you Fire your pyre around me And this place I somehow wonder if I will ever carry in that essence And if your story will ever find its break Our jagged spirits would just mesh As rusted gears I would stare at the ceiling And listen to your feet swim In ecstasy We were children of your tears </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bout</title>
      <link>/words/2011/bout/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/bout/</guid>
      <description>She dances in front of me. And I sing her praises. I watch her wail and tail. She is my goddess. She has fire and might. Completing sight. If you just see the way She breathes To me. And I in turn ignite Her forthright I’ve never seen a better dance I would never give this up No other swimmer in my cup I am the drummer to her pup Such plain expression Delightful children Spiritual premise DANCE CHILD!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>vIEW</title>
      <link>/words/2011/view/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/view/</guid>
      <description>How do I start this. Let us depart this. It’s a supple reality Full of fruits and authority. Can you not take this precious dance Too far. Encased in tar. Embarrassment too far? Let’s take a step back and review. Some view this Extraordinary behavior what does it take to make a band Of three. Might take me. Thee Some authority. AND WHEN YOU PRESS Regress. A gentle neck There’s a certain story here I’m sure it’s in the clear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slump</title>
      <link>/words/2011/slump/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/slump/</guid>
      <description>Sway sway The sands sprinkle Underneath Beige foothold arcing Rounded mounds Flowing sparks of joy Dissipating bliss breeds Grand visions The warrior arises from his Caged gluttony Gaia’s subtle song Whispering flesh In ear and mind bones A conduit of peaceful pairings Beneath these grains and above In one Encompassing Ray The warrior knows the dance To this song His feet yield The mighty blisters At Her Holy Command Sand kicks high Prepare the beast </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bright</title>
      <link>/words/2011/bright/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/bright/</guid>
      <description>Here I am Dancing in the wilderness. This secret is clutched in my grasps. I swing wildly with my right foot. I pound slightly with my left foot. They each sing the others’ praise. The dust swirls with such high regard. The long tail of wind directs beige perspective. A mound forms beneath, To the side, And on the top of its side, A cacophonoph approaches I find the right swings under me, The left swoops in front.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sun</title>
      <link>/words/2011/sun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/sun/</guid>
      <description>I want to see your thick Unapology. I want to see your best In me. Supple. Lying. In this dark bliss. The caverness. Of unyielding. Wastedness. Your eyes. In candlelight. Remind me. Of stricken gold light. And that bracelet. So unforetold. The glimmering diamond. Can I be so bold? I wish your Cadaver. Could be examined. Placed in abandon. To dance with. And holding tight. Abounding might. When you see me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wood</title>
      <link>/words/2011/wood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/wood/</guid>
      <description>When I walk her at 2AM. I feel at peace. In harmony. I resonate. When I walk her at 3AM. I am a paper sentinel. With a paper sword. When I walk her at 4AM. Her dew dresses my garment. I am at one. With this animal. We ride. I sing her discord. I wave her glee. And down her concrete stakes and wooden slabs. Along her many miles of pressed visions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharp</title>
      <link>/words/2011/sharp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/sharp/</guid>
      <description>When she closes her Mind’s eye She forgets her past. And everything. Caught in a twisted dream. I account for Her. It’s a broken mindset. But broken things Are meant to be fixed. Shifted asylum. Her heart is astray A wicked wonder. Hearing her voice again. Handshake left, and right. Are we in your crew? A crew of risk. Typing desk. Her eyes hold the sunlight Of a million moons. It’s a click on that door.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gloss</title>
      <link>/words/2011/gloss/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/gloss/</guid>
      <description>When I go into the depths of those Eyes It is like a mist And there’s this hum In my head.	There’s this brilliance. A dancing Sun. And I touch her skin. Just wanting to win. Somewhere in this Darkened Dance room. Her hips Roam with mine. Entwined. Dangerously. She tells me it’s a new day We’ll wait and see. She compliments me.	Heavily. A tear to my eye. I won’t deny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Float</title>
      <link>/words/2011/float/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/float/</guid>
      <description>You there! Little alien creature. Tell me what we’re here for. Hear for. And then. Maybe I’ll listen. Take a gander. Of your mission.	What you’re wishin’. Because, I am Like you.	Just spacin’ out.	Without a doubt. Trippin’. Wanderin’ Hopin’ we’re headin’	in the right. Direction. And when we don’t.	We don’t shout.	We don’t pout. We pontificate.	In your doubt. Wishin’ we were on that road. To nowhere. Something beautiful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Be</title>
      <link>/words/2011/be/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/be/</guid>
      <description>Truth be told Strangely Unique. She sleeps beneath my wings. Under this rock. Protectorate. Beneath my underworld. Gathering the impending storm. So dark.	So vivid. It gathers. Gathering. Like woodwork. I stare at it. Like it’s an image. Stolen from my soul. These beats in my head. I wonder where they storm from. Is it honest to steal their Meaning? Sometimes. I feel I Speak in Circles. So Let’s pick an angle And get this party Started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seem</title>
      <link>/words/2011/seem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/seem/</guid>
      <description>Her circles run coarse Around me. Coating me with Her Liquid cold fire I embrace Her Counted Shimmering blessings I pick Her favorite dance She follows. Leading Her into my circle. I pronounce Her Alive Ignited In Her ring Of flickering chaos. Wonder. I find Her bliss. She Smiles. Deep. One step too far. Never said. Never stated. She whispers selective patterns. I listen. But. The angle of my motioned feet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pounce</title>
      <link>/words/2011/pounce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2011/pounce/</guid>
      <description>She has these Starborne eyes. And I Here. on her blackened scarred beach. Face down. Spit the sand out my mouth. What happened? Where is she now? Standing over me. With that smile. And I wonder. What it meant. Don’t leave, Scorp. We need you. I. Need. You. II. Win this Holy Game. Under your covers. Left bare. The secret moment of your Life’s scare. I see your pattern. I know your fate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drop</title>
      <link>/words/2010/drop/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2010/drop/</guid>
      <description>She has Weltered walls. Shattering along Her weighted depth. Lighting dashes above. My shadow. Cascades. On Her metal Skin. I pull myself. Sword in hand. Up. Shattered. Wailing light. With careless effort, She Laughs at me. I push Up. She crashes around me. My rusted nails bite into her wasted root. I know I’m not the first. My own armored skin weighs me down. With great flair she brushes And shrugs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chirp</title>
      <link>/words/2010/chirp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2010/chirp/</guid>
      <description>Look at all this green.
Like a wall.
Like a fortress.
Boxed in.
So green.
So close.
And the chirps.
Chipper-chirper.
I count 5 birds.
2 here.
3 there.
This one over here stops when I walk this way.
This one over here stops when I listen too closely.
Like an old-skool hunter.
I read the Ether by chirp.
Now I sing with my new friends.
Mimic this one. I can do the tonality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kid</title>
      <link>/words/2010/kid/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2010/kid/</guid>
      <description>tabletops
dusty spirals
threaded messages
dreary eyes
coupled passings
signed bread.
broken.
rememberance
violent
times
dark times
whisper
sweet tones
placated
curves
barren trigger
soiled snake
what time
jealousy
sacred vowels
coffee beans
solemn smiles
happy heartache
bloodshot whiskers
simple pain</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dumb</title>
      <link>/words/2010/dumb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2010/dumb/</guid>
      <description>She has this
stream of power
to her
cupping her cask
while muses dance.
twelve at a time.
drop a pair of dimes.
i only watch
and wait
what will she do
next.
spindled twilight
showered moonlight
casting rays of
soaked meat
coat of indifference
and i just watch
and wait
what will i do
next
with her.
templed city atop
that twisted hill.
bullies chase up
but don&amp;rsquo;t come down</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stir</title>
      <link>/words/2010/stir/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2010/stir/</guid>
      <description>You speak to me
In such soft
Visions.
Slowly
Forming
Spines
Splining from the light
Here. Within.
Fire in my eyes.
I know You’re here.
Storm in my ears.
Peace.
Sacred land.
I dance on You.
Screaming. Rapture.
Ashes burned on
The corners of my bones.
Embracing
Subtle wonders.
Placing sacrifice.
Enraging demons from
Afar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some</title>
      <link>/words/2010/some/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2010/some/</guid>
      <description>She sort of is A Maenad The First. Dancing and talking On the Great Water Of life. And I, Well, I just watch. Scientifically. Artistically. Life-ly. I’m not sure what God she came from.	But she has my attention, now. For years now. And when she does dance. It’s to Her rhythm. I can’t help now But to keep her close. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shaft</title>
      <link>/words/2010/shaft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2010/shaft/</guid>
      <description>Some wicked caves behind me.
Sifting.
Barren lakes.
Woodened souls.
Pour.
Shadows clatter.
Casting light.
On all of me.
And here now.
Gravel in knees.
At Her altar.
Ten points of light.
Skyward towards Her singing embrace.
She slowly tugs at the Acorn
From inside.
Peering.
Branches unfurling.
Leaves
Within, I feel Her.
Once again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Break</title>
      <link>/words/2009/break/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2009/break/</guid>
      <description>As you’re here. As I am. Once broken. Now I am. Broken Once. Broken Twice. Broken Narrow. Sacrifice. Once Sunday. Twice a Crowd. Here on Sunday. Break the Clouds. Your bread on Wednesday. Your blood is Mine. Sacrifice. Sacrifice. Here I stand on your Step. Make it Mine. Here I implore your Sacred vine. Some have sacred vows to store. Me, I have none to explore. Once Sunday. Once You. Once Sunday, Once you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some</title>
      <link>/words/2009/some/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2009/some/</guid>
      <description>Dionysus. Where is bliss? Capping on your head? Such a diss. Mommy and Daddy would be so proud. But you. Make us. SUFFER! Dionysus. Where’s your bliss? Tucked inside your barren mistress. Here I slay. From boot to tower. Struck by. Mother. Suckle away. Ungrateful wench. I see your cause. Unto. Unto. Present. In your eyes. I hear your waking eyes. In your voice. Across the room. Beacons me. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bark</title>
      <link>/words/2009/bark/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2009/bark/</guid>
      <description>Certain kinda charm about her. Serendipity Lovely Glass Eye… On Her assheages Strands in the light Some sort of like wine..... Lonely sandwich On the floor Some crumbs. And a fire bird. hotter gets She Flaring greatness. Coupled sand. Packed pleasure. Beads of sound bounce around. Suppertime Draw the blinds. Hopeless love. Hopeless fissure. Crying. Breaking skyline In feast Calloused song </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peace</title>
      <link>/words/2008/peace/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2008/peace/</guid>
      <description>The Guides Circle in the gas The helium Propelled And circles Circling us In this spin. In this circle. They circle us. The guides. The gods guide the guides. Sun drips through. And these Guides. The voices. Hear them. Voices through the gas. Guides. Over and over. These guides hear us. Hear what they write. Circles and circles. Scribbles and scribbles. Years and years. They gain us. They gain it. Over and over the guides are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brand</title>
      <link>/words/2008/brand/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2008/brand/</guid>
      <description>As time passes Clouds cover the heat Rays of passion Stir and dance Form Breeds And I just rest Sifting These layers Grinding Passing Flight beckons Patience wears Something of a clock Cloak. Normal shadows Flight by And the sun That once was Echoes brilliantly Bonding Brotherhood And within deep Watered wells Lies my starry fate. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pick</title>
      <link>/words/2008/pick/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2008/pick/</guid>
      <description>She is. So. Perfectly. Sad. The drops. Of thunder. Pick. Brilliance. Apart. Her sadness. Her sadness. In me. Her sadness. Picks apart. In me. Tops of trees. In me. Tops of trees. In me. And with her tears. Breaks along. Her sadness. In me. Song of cheers. Elegance. Tears. Beautiful sadness. In me. In me. Beautiful sadness. Elegant madness. Wisdom dances. Around. Without. Counterpart. Tear apart. Trenches of tears. Cheeks and bleaks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curve</title>
      <link>/words/2008/curve/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2008/curve/</guid>
      <description>She dances along the rooftop of my mind. Blindly. And I, Blinded. Taste her. These feelings. She creates. Beats. Suddenly. Deeply. And when She looks down on me. From up there. I know. Confusion Is a friend. In times like these. Masked. Wrapped. Like a fire. Whereas. And she dances. Further along. My sacred plight. Wishes brew beside me. And this wooden stump. Nestled within my chin. Beckons. For her singing rain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creek</title>
      <link>/words/2008/creek/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2008/creek/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#39;s misty now. Outside. In here. Where there&amp;#39;s fear. Coating the lines of my Face. Bumping in the dark air. Sometimes. Light Finds its way. And I pass into the Flight of mind. Passing. Passing into my stare. They are memories now. And I wonder. Deeply. If what was meant to be. Passed into me. And here with mist in My hands. Rolling in my veins. These what once were. Passing into me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grease</title>
      <link>/words/2007/grease/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2007/grease/</guid>
      <description>Snoopin&amp;#39; around that fire. What are you doing there? --- &amp;#34;which twin was that?&amp;#34; From downtown… Nice shot! Well wouldn&amp;#39;t you know it, You weren&amp;#39;t so far off… Turns out…. … I was born a lefty… --- Here? That presence… Weird. Spectacular sirens. Ringing in her eyes. Someone special Has rung. Again. In my mind. Someone.New() Special clings to the underside of my Safehouse. And in the morning I hear her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shy</title>
      <link>/words/2006/shy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/shy/</guid>
      <description>(an)	Ha ha. Not so obvious… Hot white Starlight She doesn’t blink seem Hm.	To me. Trouble is	let’s talk a while. Trouble does. Somewhere in pull up a chair	Here.	pull your hair This pasture.	Her eyes are… Did she just say that?	What is this that I just found myself in… Seems dark And bright At the same time.	Well that was that. It is what it is. Telltale mysteries come to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ding</title>
      <link>/words/2006/ding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/ding/</guid>
      <description>Saturday night. Waiting. For her. Passive reproach. Someone’s watching. Stirring the sword. The air is sweet. Watching the beat of that drum. Doing nothing. Just being around. Doing. Nothing.	N1o2 t3h4h5i6n7g.8.9.0. Something Curious strikes a chord. That sounds mighty fine. Let’s examine that closer. Nocturnal nectar. Many rooms. Many locks. It’s interesting up here. Scary. Right now.	Not then. Now. Sweet sweet sw33t. What are you doing?	Finding did you do	something you seem	interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mean</title>
      <link>/words/2006/mean/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/mean/</guid>
      <description>Snap Pop Pop Snapple Something broke Inside of her Something hooked Whoa. Me me me. He He He. e e e Lettuce play. Verbage Of Nothing. Nothing is something. That&amp;#39;s the best I got. Suffered within that s t a t e o f m I n d State of mine. Mine mine mine. That&amp;#39;s when she smiles. And I crack. Under that bridge of ours. Can I borrow a dollar?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patch</title>
      <link>/words/2006/patch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/patch/</guid>
      <description>When our stars c o l l i d e Life is what it should be. Orbits surround us. Her Orbits surround me. Dance. Whimsical. Within. Me. Something in her air Strikes me true. Embracing I m a g I n a t I o n. Circling now … Something in here. Prickling. Stickling. Picking. Sight for a sore soul. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stem</title>
      <link>/words/2006/stem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/stem/</guid>
      <description>Push goes the boundary. push push push. the boundary does go. and when you think it&amp;#39;s far enough push a little more to see where it goes. topple topple topple the towers don&amp;#39;t stand so much for dealing with foundation of sand. the weathered clouds are building a troubled tale that makes the troubled clouds are laughing I have disturbed their wake brewbrewbrew with naked dreams and broken seams they do amuse and abuse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coin</title>
      <link>/words/2006/coin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/coin/</guid>
      <description>take off your jeans show me what you got ok now put them back on before anyone sees. your secret&amp;#39;s safe with me. here in here. show me your regimen. sit-up si t- up you&amp;#39;re cute. I like that. someone should show you a good time. very g oo o o o oo o d oo oo o o might be fun. too? let me get your number haven&amp;#39;t got one in a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prick</title>
      <link>/words/2006/prick/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/prick/</guid>
      <description>the twins are talking to the scales again as you see and read the time has come to explore some more. whether you are on b o a r d o1r n2o3t. quiver.sliver.river. thistimethistimethistime. silver? more on board this time. there is more balance this time. I have learned. this time. sometimes riddles abound and riddles abound in me the sorcerer&amp;#39;s sword rests in willowed wake. across the pond in the seas a quest it does make.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>green</title>
      <link>/words/2006/green/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/green/</guid>
      <description>The sun sits bright where she lies telling story and story about her skies. those blue skies ? a soft sadness sad a soft madness mad somehow I see her sometimes traveling foot and hoof wander wander wonder happiness rains more than not when that sad voice rains on them don&amp;#39;t be troubled don&amp;#39;t be s u d d e n l y s u l l e n ly it all seems clear to the one you knew you wanted to the one you threw away not me of course but you or wait.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tea</title>
      <link>/words/2006/tea/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/tea/</guid>
      <description>Trouble is under those wings she never saw. even under those stars. those shadows carried higher sullen wants carried thoughts maybe she wanted those. treasured tossed. memories serrated. that was some foreign country yet vaguely familiar. the lights ahead so bright so light. so tight. I can just make them when I try. try try try. southern comforts no avail when you postulate your former sail. another troubled piece of a troubled puzzle ragged edges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That</title>
      <link>/words/2006/that/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/that/</guid>
      <description>that&amp;#39;s her hairtie in the stairwell in the stairwell of my mind do I pick it up? dust it off? or do i let it sit. trouble stirs with it deep inside. stir stir stir sometimes. it&amp;#39;s hard to let go. sometimes. it&amp;#39;s hard to be me. hanging on. with her. hanging on. with me. the past. is brittle. it seems? countenance wanes. please don&amp;#39;t wane. with me. trouble is where does she begin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peak</title>
      <link>/words/2006/peak/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2006/peak/</guid>
      <description>troubled waters float this raft
from so long ago
sweetened stars from above
dance merrily below
her eyes, so beautiful
so glowing
mean everything to me
I reach for her countenance
to help balance these unbalanced
mountains in my mind
where she believed and others beamed
so callously behind
that smile
that smile
wondrous flare and charming aware
can only make me believe
I believe in her
I believe in us</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Way</title>
      <link>/words/2005/way/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/way/</guid>
      <description>and there, skin to skin our destinies pinned and there, traveled sadness residual quickness and there, something familiar stirs within us and there, something plain weaves throughout us and there, souls connect barren contact and there, I feel you read me you’ll never finish me and there, something amiss sudden, sullen abyss and here, once dancing in doubt I have finally figured you out </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sink</title>
      <link>/words/2005/sink/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/sink/</guid>
      <description>Troubled seas in those dreams
Of hers.
And I see them. So alive
In me.
Harrowed response.
Sloppy sour.
She floats. I see it.
She drifts. I feel it.
That smile is so cracked and
Twisted.
Only soft memories fly with me.
Hallowed sunlight.
Take flight
With her.
Must I once again
Drown in her waters.
Scorpio passing
Gemini drowning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tone</title>
      <link>/words/2005/tone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/tone/</guid>
      <description>suffered neuron amount of wake troubled luring a given take passing virgo mind aware having witnessed given flare outside tremors house arrest inside horrors lemming’s test circling crows fret fret fret boughs brought low a coward set shaking towers mindful light kindling sour masking chide backlit hair sundown ghost moonlight share harried most haggard notions tired sake midnight nations sacred take </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step</title>
      <link>/words/2005/step/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/step/</guid>
      <description>hollowed shining ringing her echoes she refines that which is there forever entwined and enwrapped and furrowed and programmed within the great divide until we know how long it is with the other side, I won’t know and that sort of scares the essence of spirited debate and heart and how can that know if I don’t know the essence of me. search and search and search I may wander aimlessly are you ok with that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wide</title>
      <link>/words/2005/wide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/wide/</guid>
      <description>hands reached out the blue dances blindly around my fingertips around her. around us. I see her shining through through closed eyes. she smiles so peacefully on my bliss. traveling from fields of wandering green we hold each other forever. forever. the wind smiles on us too together we were meant to be. together with that harmony. this is some dance. she follows my lead. I know that this is where we are meant to be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Murk</title>
      <link>/words/2005/murk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/murk/</guid>
      <description>there’s wild water in that brown-eyed whirlwind I must confess, if it were any differently I would rescind. my sails will snag upon her force but I know it won’t take me far. for I have only traveled these waters mapped by other stars. troubled waters in a different time troubled waters these will be mine she’ll dash me further than I’ve been before. she’ll throw me further than my plans in store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Link</title>
      <link>/words/2005/link/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/link/</guid>
      <description>the look in her eye makes me wonder if her story is deep within me traveling vast levels spiraling down my spine that smile so weak trembling off that corner haunting past must be it don’t unlock it makes it worse climb that mountain now that’s an adventure ah, her trials so innocent and i’m so guilty that look of hers is the look of mine </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Try</title>
      <link>/words/2005/try/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/try/</guid>
      <description>look in my eyes tell me how much you hate this game as you make your next move as you try to beat me chilling visions in our minds I see you before you think you see me dancing together unity prosperity illusions our reflections on bathroom floors your skin. our game is perfect don’t lie to me please. don’t stop lying to me </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beams</title>
      <link>/words/2005/beams/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/beams/</guid>
      <description>what I miss most of all are those times in that underbrush with you those rocks. that September mist together under that sunlight playing with those autumn leaves it was there that I found god in your wake I felt your heat against mine For the first time beautiful things beautiful you our hands so young and pure that sweater of yours that’s right I cut my foot that one time, didn’t i?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mold</title>
      <link>/words/2005/mold/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/mold/</guid>
      <description>stroke of impatience stroke of genius I am finally settling into the person you crafted me with great care and jealousy great precision ////settling//into//you///// ////settling//into//you///// that’s what you want isn’t it? puzzle pieces fill me and that’s all they are these creases in my smile lined by the jigsaw not a star not a sky trailing in your delight I envy that smile smile more prickly sensations behind my eyes so true so blue to be like you so not me but the me you want me to be </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temp</title>
      <link>/words/2005/temp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/temp/</guid>
      <description>it’s crazy outside and she’s in here with me crazy in here too. wandering in that forest once again. paths in hundreds of directions of paths the trees dream of me anything to be their hero her smile seems so far away from the likes of me bathing in tragedy I am rife with brooding tendrils </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Won</title>
      <link>/words/2005/won/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/won/</guid>
      <description>reach out to me you’ll see you’ll see forest in daylight I’ll be there do you care? won’t you share? why don’t you call me sounds kinda cool doesn’t it together we’ll go out see what it’s about reaching. I see that hand. oh there it is again. quite the stretch is there a reason for the riddle? oh it’s your riddle I should have known. it’s a tricky one, I see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plank</title>
      <link>/words/2005/plank/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/plank/</guid>
      <description>one by one she pops the stars in my eyes in the needle goes slowly through my brown skies a prick a stick wincing yet grinning she twists that needle so true and straight watching me squirm without much debate I kick and yell and beg for more I yearn to know what she has in store I barter for her pain like a fool taking me to her school excrement in her stool I smell like a fat fool with a little drool spin that metal how I jerk in glee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grain</title>
      <link>/words/2005/grain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/grain/</guid>
      <description>my wrinkled shriveled carcass washes up
against her salty sand.
seeping into my cuts and sores,
her jagged rocks
rip and stretch my haggard meat.
and cut against my chipping bones.
on her sea of grains, crabs claw at my fingernails
they pull and tug until i snap with satisfaction.
birds,
once singing with our great harmony
now pick at my eyes with
infected beaks.
they clip the whites of my eyes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miss</title>
      <link>/words/2005/miss/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/miss/</guid>
      <description>fettered quickly upon her barren shores I know what’s best for her and her smile sinking quickly beneath me. she sings a song I do not know or have never heard. what’s to know about her? about us? fine day for a matinee. I say. surely in the quick of dawn. we are one chances are we. chances are we. chances are we. who said we never owe a creature&amp;#39;s stow perchance it’s happenstance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Say</title>
      <link>/words/2005/say/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/say/</guid>
      <description>how do I show her
the light in my sky?
without showing her</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wick</title>
      <link>/words/2005/wick/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/wick/</guid>
      <description>release that grass into your minions patience is a virtue. your virtue. not mine. making sense yet? in a multitude of perfection. quite the tower you have here. showered yet? trouble lurks underwater, I understand. no, I don’t. stretch into the mindscape of your sandscape.that’snotaword. i hear you, but don’t want to. aren’t you gone yet? shake that web server just a little more stop wearing my underwear. question that chimpmonk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wind</title>
      <link>/words/2005/wind/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2005/wind/</guid>
      <description>Step into my sling. if you dare. For it’s a fun ride to ride. for a while. I admit. Maybe you should try? Just once? On you hop and Around and round we go. A blur it becomes. A flurry it yields. Where it stops. Only I know. For you’re in my sling. My witty ride. My complex side. Slide and twist. Isn’t this fun? Squirm and yell. Are you done?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blow</title>
      <link>/words/1995/blow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 1995 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/1995/blow/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever. felt? The wind from. a thirsty. barren. wasteland. flow over you? like a disease that won&amp;#39;t decay. then notice. out of nowhere. you&amp;#39;re there!	in the wasteland. looking staring at the void. the dunes of hollow. wondering what was once there. by then, it happens? you notice. You are the wasteland. spewing your wicked, decaying, breath. wind. on others. does this stop? will it end? the wind is speechless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sad</title>
      <link>/words/1995/sad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 1995 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/1995/sad/</guid>
      <description>O harketh! Such a sad, sad day cometh! It IS heard. let us, me, fully embrace. the drink is sweet. yet taste is bitter! Such the sad, sad day Rises! Can it be toppled? it reigns the sons and daughters, me. echoes through the valleys makes the grass ShUdDeR. So much so, the pain. Such pain shatters. My existence, reality questioned. What lives of my being without such pain? O how such sad, sad days are suppressed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trench</title>
      <link>/words/1995/trench/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 1995 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/1995/trench/</guid>
      <description>what small pellets.
THE FORCE IN ITS POSSESION.
each unique, yet fiercely potent.
THE STREAM, OH, MY DEAR, DEAR STREAM!!!!!
the naive, small stream.
LOOK, BE AWARE!!!!
your substance can crush you.
BREAK YOU DOWN!
underground.
DO YOU HEAR THE WARNING?
no, the innocence is taken for granted.
DO YOU SEE WHAT YOU ARE BLIND TO?
hear THIS then, your doom is roaring to you.
YOUR DEATH!!
the killing sound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Birds</title>
      <link>/words/1995/birds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 1995 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/1995/birds/</guid>
      <description>can i see behind those lines?
it is hard. and it is
tricky to do.
i see to and want.
to know?
do you see me?
do you see behind this
curved line
on my head
that some
claim
a smile?
do you see that it&amp;rsquo;s a wince that makes my face that way.
do you see
that
pain that&amp;rsquo;s wedged within me.
Foolish! How could I have done this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chain</title>
      <link>/words/1995/chain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 1995 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/1995/chain/</guid>
      <description>is this a joke? a rotten, putrid, sulfuric acidic silly, corrupt threatening joke? to make me fall. hard to the ground. i want to be near you, do you see? to be close to someone i hardly know. but do know, just the,same/ your hand is so far away. i can&amp;#39;t see it. through it. are you thinking of me. this forgotten chamber locked in my chest, must know. tonight. of lifelessness the rhythm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strain</title>
      <link>/words/1995/strain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 1995 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/1995/strain/</guid>
      <description>I know n o t where this tree has
gone.
was it not alive when i got here last?
breathed here last?
death is all it is!
decayed like a black stain on the earth.
me.
i look all around, and it still stands.
it still stands!
but lifelessness consumes it.
breaching it like death.
the bushes are trampled underground!
they stand no longer. i travel
across the street, to meet</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gaze</title>
      <link>/words/1995/gaze/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 1995 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/1995/gaze/</guid>
      <description>I look into THis cRAZY thing. DOes it work? I do not see MySelf. Blackness. Darkness! Void. Nothing! I realize now that is what Iv&amp;#39;e BECOMe No, it is WoRking just fine it is I that is wrong AGaiN So what AM i to do? Where do i go? just stand. here. alone. by the mirror. holding it tight. it is all i have. isn&amp;#39;t it? that i am UNAWARE. is there light?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perch</title>
      <link>/words/1995/perch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 1995 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/1995/perch/</guid>
      <description>charging. Breathing. am i perhaps, alive. in You? can i be? I want to. but i don&amp;#39;t see it. a year seems so long, yet so so far away, a desolate country. but time makes you desolate right? </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bell</title>
      <link>/words/1995/bell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 1995 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/1995/bell/</guid>
      <description>There is a light that I see, only partially. I want it. how do I get it? one might ask me. i try, but it&amp;#39;s just out of reach. i hear a bell, love. i know not where it comes, but i want it please, i need help. can you see for me. a light shines and a bell rings, but is it for me? i feel it is, reaching for me, i can pull in, if i had the sight the moon, can i stand stand alone with it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coil</title>
      <link>/words/1995/coil/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 1995 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/1995/coil/</guid>
      <description>the youth now
is far
greater
than my
heart once
conceived
Perceived.
i must.
what i am now.
think now.
reconstruct.
me.
my life.
for tomorrow.
for another
life.
the past
is what i behold
tightly
within me. through me. part of
me.
to let go is deaTH.
i do not desire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Words</title>
      <link>/words/1995/words/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 1995 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/1995/words/</guid>
      <description>these words.
do they have,
possess,
power?
some wish not.
some die so.
they must.
how could i explain
you
if they couldn&amp;rsquo;t.
idieSo.
they mean
everything to me.
yet they are only symbols.
but they are me.
can i not express myself
so openly. so profoundly.
i need this word. this
power.
and i need you.
too.
is that wrong, as well.
i die so.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
