<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2019 on ossem: a creative space</title>
    <link>/year/2019/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2019 on ossem: a creative space</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/year/2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pi</title>
      <link>/sketches/pi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sketches/pi/</guid>
      <description>She has presences In the Electric view A blinding stew … of plight and magic … A diplomatic Coefficient Bristled into Her Majestic (and few) (This is my first digital drawing, done on Leonardo. The character is based on Loish&amp;rsquo;s Huntress, which is easily my favorite work of hers. I liked it so much that I felt the need to mimic it and finally give this whole digital art thing a try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rough</title>
      <link>/words/2019/rough/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2019/rough/</guid>
      <description>High on Human So very High on Human Yeah, I&amp;#39;m High on Human So many stories and victories The agony And yeah, the drama You know it feeds the Momma This Human High So high! Why fight it (Just live it) Death is withdrawal Birth the next hit No questions now This Human got me crazy lit! High! So high, man Oh, the Human High High on Human Set sails So fairy tale Don&amp;#39;t dwell Ride the Human High &amp;amp; Its blazed-out swell Oh man High as a kite again Thank you, Human Where you been?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heart</title>
      <link>/words/2019/heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2019/heart/</guid>
      <description>It seems so long ago Yet yesterday All the way from the dusk and dawn and dusk again The moon and alleyways Walking past That police car, and trying my best to look n	o	r	m	a	l And then you entered As a Shamaness A fortuneteller And spoke to me In Truth and Majesty In plain words And riddles, too Yes, we spoke in two planes That night In the real and In the surreal (visceral) The problems in the village Were the problems in me .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>