<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2008 on ossem: a creative space</title>
    <link>/year/2008/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2008 on ossem: a creative space</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/year/2008/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Peace</title>
      <link>/words/2008/peace/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2008/peace/</guid>
      <description>The Guides Circle in the gas The helium Propelled And circles Circling us In this spin. In this circle. They circle us. The guides. The gods guide the guides. Sun drips through. And these Guides. The voices. Hear them. Voices through the gas. Guides. Over and over. These guides hear us. Hear what they write. Circles and circles. Scribbles and scribbles. Years and years. They gain us. They gain it. Over and over the guides are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brand</title>
      <link>/words/2008/brand/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2008/brand/</guid>
      <description>As time passes Clouds cover the heat Rays of passion Stir and dance Form Breeds And I just rest Sifting These layers Grinding Passing Flight beckons Patience wears Something of a clock Cloak. Normal shadows Flight by And the sun That once was Echoes brilliantly Bonding Brotherhood And within deep Watered wells Lies my starry fate. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pick</title>
      <link>/words/2008/pick/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2008/pick/</guid>
      <description>She is. So. Perfectly. Sad. The drops. Of thunder. Pick. Brilliance. Apart. Her sadness. Her sadness. In me. Her sadness. Picks apart. In me. Tops of trees. In me. Tops of trees. In me. And with her tears. Breaks along. Her sadness. In me. Song of cheers. Elegance. Tears. Beautiful sadness. In me. In me. Beautiful sadness. Elegant madness. Wisdom dances. Around. Without. Counterpart. Tear apart. Trenches of tears. Cheeks and bleaks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curve</title>
      <link>/words/2008/curve/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2008/curve/</guid>
      <description>She dances along the rooftop of my mind. Blindly. And I, Blinded. Taste her. These feelings. She creates. Beats. Suddenly. Deeply. And when She looks down on me. From up there. I know. Confusion Is a friend. In times like these. Masked. Wrapped. Like a fire. Whereas. And she dances. Further along. My sacred plight. Wishes brew beside me. And this wooden stump. Nestled within my chin. Beckons. For her singing rain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creek</title>
      <link>/words/2008/creek/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/words/2008/creek/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#39;s misty now. Outside. In here. Where there&amp;#39;s fear. Coating the lines of my Face. Bumping in the dark air. Sometimes. Light Finds its way. And I pass into the Flight of mind. Passing. Passing into my stare. They are memories now. And I wonder. Deeply. If what was meant to be. Passed into me. And here with mist in My hands. Rolling in my veins. These what once were. Passing into me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
