<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stories on ossem: a creative space</title>
    <link>/stories/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stories on ossem: a creative space</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/stories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Side</title>
      <link>/stories/2018/side/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2018/side/</guid>
      <description>With the monitors flickering upon his nearby, dark environment, Ron then wondered further that if the very reality that he is currently experiencing now is indeed a simulation of some sort &amp;ndash; with technology accelerating at a seemingly accelerating rate &amp;ndash; would it eventually culminate in the ability to accurately reflect the reality that Ron was in now?
The idea struck Ron. Is the reality that Ron finds himself in now a result of jumping into a technology or program that started in the same way as he is currently experiencing?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grind</title>
      <link>/stories/2018/grind/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2018/grind/</guid>
      <description>(Based on an actual event.)
 “DID ANYONE CALL 911?!” I screamed as I jumped out of my car.
“YES,” a voice rang out plainly to me. I felt stupid for asking. It would end up being my only contribution towards the entire disaster.
The man in his car behind me – Kenneth, I would like to say – had just gotten out of his own vehicle and ran resolutely to the aid of whoever was trapped in the flipped over cold, blue car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stare</title>
      <link>/stories/2007/stare/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2007/stare/</guid>
      <description>Still. Those eyes are what I&amp;rsquo;ll remember: piercing, intense. If anything it was if he was telling me something on a much different level than anything I had been accustomed to. I got the sense we were playing an intergalactic game of tag and he had just stuck it to me good, as if to say &amp;ldquo;gotcha, you lucky bastard. This time it&amp;rsquo;s your turn.&amp;rdquo; On a certain level I understood him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crisp</title>
      <link>/stories/2006/crisp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2006/crisp/</guid>
      <description>Still, the subtle scent of tobacco in the air snapped at the tip of Roger&amp;rsquo;s nose. It made him nervous somehow, but he managed to keep his composure. He could tell by the way his clothes were sticking to his body it had to have been about 4a.m. But you couldn&amp;rsquo;t tell that by the scenery around him. Life abounded. He wasn&amp;rsquo;t quite sure how he got here, or even which hotel he was in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Race</title>
      <link>/stories/2006/race/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2006/race/</guid>
      <description>Harry couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but to reflect on what he just saw. He felt the need to shake his head a bit. It was as if a cobweb had enveloped his mind, causing him to shake and grind in a somewhat hurried discourse.
So Harry did hurry along his merry way. But still. What was it that he just saw? If he thought about it some more, would it change? Would he somehow begin to see his own mind and its own capacities in a different light?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crack</title>
      <link>/stories/2006/crack/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2006/crack/</guid>
      <description>Richard peered steadfastly into the sidewalk. It seemed barren somehow. As if a robber had broken in the middle of the night and swiped it of its character. The ridges speckled its plain face, smoothing in and out of a multitude of wrinkled pores.
A squint broke out over the ridge of Richard&amp;rsquo;s face. It was as if were dancing with a perplexing notion, waning in and out of tepid consciousness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speck</title>
      <link>/stories/2006/speck/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2006/speck/</guid>
      <description>With finality, the chair struck the bare wood floor. The air had no choice but to snap at first, but slowly it helped the chair down into oblivion. The weave of space and time undulated with a warm grace that offered a wishful eye and a careful stare of her newfound decision.
The creaking of the rope-spawn tendrils from high above tightened so sharply. Reverberations of past cries could only make their way into the current web of the room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slopes</title>
      <link>/stories/2006/slopes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2006/slopes/</guid>
      <description>As I got ready to leave to say my goodbyes, I noticed she got up to head upstairs before me. It was curious behavior, consistent with what I’ve seen from her all night. I made my round, hugging each person who had touched my life this clear misty morning. The subtle shadows of pine needles from the outside greens were starting to darken on the nearby windows. The sun was creeping into our consciousness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glow</title>
      <link>/stories/2006/glow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2006/glow/</guid>
      <description>Before I turned off the light to the room, I looked at the Buddha sitting on the shelf. He looked happy, as always; a certain vein of content flowed through the little statue. On this night I sort of related to the fellow. I sat there for a split second, captured and almost frozen, looking deep into his smile. A certain part of me saw myself in that chubby little cherub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pick</title>
      <link>/stories/2006/pick/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2006/pick/</guid>
      <description>I opened the door and was immediately confused on how I should feel. The little shop was more crowded than any time I had seen it. I could only guess the age group. Junior High? High school? I didn’t see any adults. A youth group, maybe?
The door closed behind me and I felt the old familiar rush of anxiety that I was the center of attention as everyone took a look at me to size me up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strap</title>
      <link>/stories/2006/strap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2006/strap/</guid>
      <description>The phone call was simple enough. She called to thank me. It was an innocent, innocuous moment, but something told me that I had just encountered a significant point in my life. It was almost as if I had passed a great moral test of some sort. I never met her, but here she was, thanking me in broken English. “Thank you, Greg. Thank you.”
It was almost as if life itself, in some sort of twisted incarnation, was telling me something pivotal – something meaningful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hail</title>
      <link>/stories/2005/hail/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2005/hail/</guid>
      <description>And there, walking along side of the parking building, Roger knew he was about to taste destiny.
Roger was on his way to pick up some friends for the night out. They lived in a busy part of downtown. People lined the streets one either side, causing traffic to snarl its way throughout. Roger had just parked his car in the parking structure to the right of him and was on his way to his friends’ apartment two blocks south.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ray</title>
      <link>/stories/2005/ray/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2005/ray/</guid>
      <description>And there, exiting that bustling restaurant, Ray felt a certain sense deep within that he hadn’t felt for some time. In a way, he felt that he had been shifted in some way, some way deep inside.
His friends were well on their way to their cars, but Ray couldn’t help but to wonder if they themselves were touched in the same manner he was. It was as if their conversation had impacted him in a way that will be with him for the rest of his life, perhaps in the final days of death, when all who surround him are nameless unrecognizable creatures of care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jon</title>
      <link>/stories/2005/jon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2005/jon/</guid>
      <description>And when Jon finished wiping the mirror with that dampened hand-towel of his, he felt that somehow his life had changed. Something deep within that mirror struck back at him. There wasn’t a familiar reflection that lived within the mirror this morning. No, this morning Jon saw the very thing that looked back at him. He couldn’t help but to look back. It called into him to stare it in the eyes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>George</title>
      <link>/stories/2005/george/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stories/2005/george/</guid>
      <description>And it was there with those eyes that George knew he made his mistake. Looking around with all these strangers, he could only grasp his memory by mere threads. How did he get here? Where were his friends? Where was he?
So many people bristled at his presence in that old rusted house, the muffled music made him confused on whether he should be happy or sad. People stopped briefly in the hallway to dispense somewhat honest conversations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
